<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<Specialties>
    <element>
        <actor>Sports Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Sports Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in sport injury related physical therapy.</description>
        <name>Sports Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>sport-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sports Vision Optometrist</actor>
        <actors>Sports Vision Optometrists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Specializes in sport related eye injuries and treatments.</description>
        <name>Sports Vision</name>
        <uid>sports-vision-optometrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Surgery Hospice and Palliative Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Surgery Hospice and Palliative Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A surgeon with special knowledge and skills to prevent and relieve the
            suffering experienced by patients with life-limiting illnesses. This specialist works
            with an interdisciplinary hospice or palliative care team to maximize quality of life
            while addressing physical, psychological, social and spiritual needs of both patient and
            family throughout the course of the disease, through the dying process, and beyond for
            the family. This specialist has expertise in the assessment of patients with advanced
            disease; the relief of distressing symptoms; the coordination of interdisciplinary
            patient and family-centered care in diverse venues; the use of specialized care systems
            including hospice; the management of the imminently dying patient; and legal and ethical
            decision making in end-of-life care.
        </description>
        <name>Surgery Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>surgery-hospice-and-palliative-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sleep Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Sleep Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in sleep disorders.</description>
        <name>Sleep Medicine</name>
        <uid>sleep-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Therapeutic Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Therapeutic Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the treatment of cancer and other diseases with radiation.
        </description>
        <name>Therapeutic Radiology</name>
        <uid>therapeutic-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Speech Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Speech Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in speech therapy.</description>
        <name>Speech Therapy</name>
        <uid>speech-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Spinal Cord Injury Physiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Spinal Cord Injury Physiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in patients with spinal cord injuries.</description>
        <name>Spinal Cord Injury Medicine</name>
        <uid>spinal-cord-injury-physiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Legal Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Legal Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Legal Medicine is a special field of medicine that focuses on various aspects
            of medicine and law. Historically, the practice of legal medicine made contributions to
            medicine as a scientific instrument to solve criminal perplexities. Since World War II,
            the domain of legal medicine has broadened to include not only aspects of medical
            science to solve legal and criminal problems but aspects of law as it applies to
            medicine. Legal Medicine continues to grow as medicolegal issues like medical
            malpractice and liability, government regulation of health care, issues of tort reform,
            and moral and ethical complexities presented by technological advances become
            increasingly prominent. Many medical schools have implemented courses which supply
            medicolegal instruction for medical students, and many law schools now offer medicolegal
            courses. Also, dual degree programs in law and medicine have been created to assist
            physicians to bridge the gap between medicine and the law.
        </description>
        <name>Legal Medicine</name>
        <uid>legal-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Medical Examiner Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Medical Examiner Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Medical Examiner</name>
        <uid>medical-examiner-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Mental Health Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Mental Health Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in mental health.</description>
        <name>Psych/Mental Health Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>mental-health-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Micrographic Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Micrographic Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in removing diseased skin via surgical methods.</description>
        <name>MOHS-Micrographic Surgery</name>
        <uid>micrographic-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neuropathologist</actor>
        <actors>Neuropathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnosing nervous system diseases.</description>
        <name>Neuropathology</name>
        <uid>neuropathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Nuclear Cardiologist</actor>
        <actors>Nuclear Cardiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnosing and treating diseases with radioactive materials.
        </description>
        <name>Nuclear Cardiology</name>
        <uid>nuclear-cardiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Nuclear Imaging &amp; Therapy Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Nuclear Imaging &amp; Therapy Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnosing and treating diseases with radioactive materials.
        </description>
        <name>Nuclear Imaging &amp; Therapy</name>
        <uid>nuclear-imaging-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in occupational preventive care.</description>
        <name>Occupational Medicine</name>
        <uid>occupational-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Body Imaging Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Body Imaging Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in body imaging.</description>
        <name>Body Imaging</name>
        <uid>body-imaging-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Critical Care OBGYN</actor>
        <actors>Critical Care OBGYNS</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in critical care diagnoses and treatment.</description>
        <name>Critical Care Medicine OBGYN</name>
        <uid>critical-care-obgyn</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dental Laboratory Technician</actor>
        <actors>Dental Laboratory Technicians</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>An individual who has the skill and knowledge in the fabrication of dental
            appliances, prostheses and devices in accordance with a dentist's laboratory work
            authorization. To avoid misleading the public, no occupational title other than dental
            laboratory technician or certified dental technician (when appropriate) should be used
            to describe this auxiliary.
        </description>
        <name>Dental Laboratory Technician</name>
        <uid>dental-laboratory-technician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dental Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Dental Therapists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>A Dental Therapist is an individual who has completed an accredited or
            non-accredited dental therapy program and who has been authorized by the relevant state
            board or a tribal entity to provide services within the scope of their practice under
            the supervision of a dentist. Functions that may be delegated to the dental therapist
            vary based on the needs of the dentist, the educational preparation of the dental
            therapist and state dental practice acts and regulations.
        </description>
        <name>Dental Therapist</name>
        <uid>dental-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dentist</actor>
        <actors>Dentists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in teeth and oral health.</description>
        <name>Dentistry</name>
        <uid>dentist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Pathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of tissue and bodily fluids.</description>
        <name>Clinical Pathology</name>
        <uid>clinical-pathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Allergist</actor>
        <actors>Allergists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Allergy &amp; Immunology Allergy</name>
        <uid>allergy-immunology-allergy</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Group Psychotherapy Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Group Psychotherapy Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in counceling and therapy in groups.</description>
        <name>Group Psychotherapy</name>
        <uid>group-psychotherapy-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunology</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An internal medicine physician who specializes in clinical and laboratory
            immunology disease management.
        </description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunology</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-clinical-laboratory-immunology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Immunodermatologist</actor>
        <actors>Immunodermatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnoses of the body's immune system by laboratory
            procedures.
        </description>
        <name>Clinical &amp; Laboratory Dermatological Immunology</name>
        <uid>immunodermatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dermatologist</actor>
        <actors>Dermatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in skin disorders, including moles and melanoma.</description>
        <name>Dermatology</name>
        <uid>dermatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dermatopathologist</actor>
        <actors>Dermatopathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of skin.</description>
        <name>Dermatopathology</name>
        <uid>dermatopathology-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapy Assistant</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapy Assistants</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>An occupational therapy assistant is a person who has graduated from an
            occupational therapy assistant program accredited by the Accreditation Council for
            Occupational Therapy Education (ACOTE) or predecessor organizations, has successfully
            completed a period of supervised fieldwork experience required by the accredited
            occupational therapy assistant program, has passed a nationally recognized entry-level
            examination for occupational therapy assistants, and fulfills state requirements for
            licensure, certification, or registration. An occupational therapy assistant provides
            interventions under the supervision of an occupational therapist which emphasize the
            therapeutic use of everyday life activities (i.e., occupations) with individuals or
            groups for the purpose of facilitating participation in roles and situations and in
            home, school, workplace, community and other settings. Occupational therapy services are
            provided for the purpose of promoting health and wellness and are provided to those who
            have or are at risk for developing an illness, injury, disease, disorder, condition,
            impairment, disability, activity limitation, or participation restriction. Occupational
            therapy assistants address the physical, cognitive, psychosocial, sensory, and other
            aspects of occupational performance in a variety of contexts to support engagement in
            everyday life activities that affect health, well-being, and quality of life.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapy Assistant</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapy-assistant</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapy Assistant Feeding, Eating &amp; Swallowing</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapy Assistant Feeding, Eating &amp; Swallowings</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapy assistants provide environmental modifications under the
            supervision of an occupational therapist. OTAs develop and implement an individualized
            occupational therapy environmental modification plan that reflects the relevant contexts
            of the client and relevant others and maximizes current and future occupational
            performance, safety, and participation of the client. Clients receive environmental
            modification recommendations and interventions that enable them to meet occupational
            performance and participation goals and that have adequate flexibility to accommodate
            for their future needs.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapy Assistant Feeding, Eating &amp; Swallowing</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapy-assistant-feeding-eating-swallowing</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapy Assistant Low Vision</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapy Assistant Low Visions</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapy assistants contribute to the completion of an
            individualized occupational therapy low-vision evaluation under the direction and
            supervision of the occupational therapist to identify factors that may facilitate,
            compensate for, or inhibit use of vision in occupational performance. Clients are
            engaged in the identification of strengths, limitations, and goals as they relate to low
            vision to optimize independence and participation in desired occupations. Occupational
            therapy assistants also contribute to the development and implementation of an
            individualized occupational therapy low-vision intervention plan in collaboration with
            the occupational therapist, client, and relevant others that reflects the client's
            priorities for occupational performance.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapy Assistant Low Vision</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapy-assistant-low-vision</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapy Assistant Driving and Community Mobility</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapy Assistant Driving and Community Mobilities</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapy assistants contribute to the completion of an
            individualized occupational therapy driving and community mobility evaluation by
            administering delegated assessments and identifying findings that impact the client's
            occupational performance. Clients engage in the assessment and occupational profile
            process to customize the evaluation to their individual driving and community mobility
            needs. Occupational therapy assistants administer and continuously modify individualized
            in-vehicle and community mobility assessments within the naturalistic context of the
            community in response to the occupational performance and safety behaviors of the
            client. They also implement an individualized intervention plan, within the parameters
            established in collaboration with the occupational therapist that reflects the contexts
            of the client and meets his or her occupational performance and safety needs.
            Occupational therapy assistants address immediate and long-term implications of
            psychosocial issues related to compromised driving and community mobility throughout the
            occupational therapy process and makes recommendations to the occupational therapist for
            modification to service delivery.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapy Assistant Driving and Community Mobility</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapy-assistant-driving-and-community-mobility</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Urologist</actor>
        <actors>Urologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in genital and urinary problems.</description>
        <name>Urology</name>
        <uid>urologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Vision Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Vision Therapists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Specializes in therapies to help improve vision.</description>
        <name>Vision Therapy</name>
        <uid>vision-therapy-optometrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Oral Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Oral Pathologists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in identification of oral diseases.</description>
        <name>Oral and Maxillofacial Pathology</name>
        <uid>oral-pathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Oral Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Oral Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in surgical operations of the mouth, jaw and face.</description>
        <name>Oral &amp; Maxillofacial Surgery</name>
        <uid>oral-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pain Management Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Pain Management Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in pain management and prevention.</description>
        <name>Pain Medicine</name>
        <uid>pain-management-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Pediatrics</name>
        <uid>pediatric-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatrics Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatrics Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's physical therapy.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>pediatric-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Rheumatologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Rheumatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's joints, muscles, bones and tendons.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Rheumatology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-rheumatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Pulmonologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Pulmonologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's lungs and airways.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Pulmonology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-pulmonologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Dermatologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Dermatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's skin disorders, including moles and melanoma.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Dermatology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-dermatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Blood Banking &amp; Transfusion Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Blood Banking &amp; Transfusion Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in blood transfusion and banking.</description>
        <name>Blood Banking &amp; Transfusion Medicine</name>
        <uid>blood-banking-transfusion-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Ear, Nose and Throat Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Ear, Nose and Throat Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in ear, nose and throat problems.</description>
        <name>Otolaryngology</name>
        <uid>ear-nose-throat-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Facial Plastic Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Facial Plastic Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in facial, plastic and reconstructive surgery.</description>
        <name>Facial Plastic Surgery</name>
        <uid>facial-plastic-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Medical Microbiologist</actor>
        <actors>Medical Microbiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in viruses and bacteria that cause diseases.</description>
        <name>Medical Microbiology</name>
        <uid>medical-microbiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Medicine Hospice and Palliative Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Family Medicine Hospice and Palliative Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A family medicine physician with special knowledge and skills to prevent and
            relieve the suffering experienced by patients with life-limiting illnesses. This
            specialist works with an interdisciplinary hospice or palliative care team to maximize
            quality of life while addressing physical, psychological, social and spiritual needs of
            both patient and family throughout the course of the disease, through the dying process,
            and beyond for the family. This specialist has expertise in the assessment of patients
            with advanced disease; the relief of distressing symptoms; the coordination of
            interdisciplinary patient and family-centered care in diverse venues; the use of
            specialized care systems including hospice; the management of the imminently dying
            patient; and legal and ethical decision making in end-of-life care.
        </description>
        <name>Family Medicine Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>family-medicine-hospice-and-palliative-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Low Vision Rehabilitation Optometrist</actor>
        <actors>Low Vision Rehabilitation Optometrists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Specializes in treating patients with very poor vision.</description>
        <name>Low Vision Rehabilitation</name>
        <uid>low-vision-rehabilitation-optometrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Medicine Sleep Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Family Medicine Sleep Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A Family Medicine Physician who practices Sleep Medicine is certified in the
            subspecialty of sleep medicine and specializes in the clinical assessment, physiologic
            testing, diagnosis, management and prevention of sleep and circadian rhythm disorders.
            Sleep specialists treat patients of any age and use multidisciplinary approaches.
            Disorders managed by sleep specialists include, but are not limited to, sleep related
            breathing disorders, insomnia, hypersomnias, circadian rhythm sleep disorders,
            parasomnias and sleep related movement disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Family Medicine Sleep Medicine</name>
        <uid>family-medicine-sleep-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in imaging of children via X-rays and ultrasound.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Radiology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Rehabilitation Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Rehabilitation Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Rehabilitation</name>
        <uid>rehabilitation-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Radiology Podiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Radiology Podiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in foot and ankle imaging.</description>
        <name>Radiology Podiatry</name>
        <uid>radiology-podiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Forensic Psychiatry</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Forensic Psychiatries</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Forensic Psychiatry is a subspecialty with psychiatric focus on
            interrelationships with civil, criminal and administrative law, evaluation and
            specialized treatment of individuals involved with the legal system, incarcerated in
            jails, prisons, and forensic psychiatry hospitals.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Forensic Psychiatry</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-forensic-psychiatry</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pulmonary Function Technologist</actor>
        <actors>Pulmonary Function Technologists</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>An individual who is trained and qualified to perform pulmonary diagnostic
            tests. In the course of conducting these tests, the Pulmonary Function Technologist is
            able to setup, calibrate, maintain, and ensure the quality assurance of the pulmonary
            function testing equipment. In the laboratory, clinical or patient care setting the
            technologist instructs patients, elicits cooperation, performs procedures, monitors
            patient response, and evaluates patient performance. Tests results are calculated,
            compared with predicted normal ranges, and evaluated for reliability. The technologist
            collects clinical history data and evaluates the clinical implications of the test
            results.
        </description>
        <name>Pulmonary Function Technologist</name>
        <uid>pulmonary-function-technologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Primary Care Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Primary Care Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in your and your family's health.</description>
        <name>Primary Care Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>primary-care-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Professional Counselor</actor>
        <actors>Professional Counselors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in professional counseling counseling.</description>
        <name>Professional Counseling</name>
        <uid>professional-counselor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnosis and treatment of mental disorders.</description>
        <name>Psychiatry</name>
        <uid>psychiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Addiction Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Addiction Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A doctor of osteopathy board eligible/certified in the field of Psychiatry by
            the American Osteopathic Board of Neurology and Psychiatry is able to obtain a
            Certificate of Added Qualifications in the field of Addiction Medicine
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Addiction Medicine</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-addiction-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Phlebologist</actor>
        <actors>Phlebologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Phlebology is the medical discipline that involves the diagnosis and treatment
            of venous disorders, including spider veins, varicose veins, chronic venous
            insufficiency, venous leg ulcers, congenital venous abnormalities, venous
            thromboembolism and other disorders of venous origin. A phlebologist has attained a
            minimum of 50 hours of CME units in phlebology-related courses, and is knowledgeable of
            and trained in a variety of diagnostic techniques including physical examination, venous
            imaging techniques such as duplex ultrasound, CT and MR, plethysmographic techniques and
            laboratory evaluation related to venous thromboembolism. The phlebologist is also
            trained in a variety of therapeutic interventions, which may include compression,
            sclerotherapy, cutaneous vascular laser, endovenous thermoablation procedures (laser and
            radiofrequency) endovenous chemical ablation, surgical procedures (e.g., ambulatory
            phlebectomy, venous ligation), vasoactive medications and the management of venous
            thromboembolism.
        </description>
        <name>Phlebology</name>
        <uid>phlebology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Physiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Physiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in treating patients with physical disabilities.</description>
        <name>Physical Medicine &amp; Rehabilitation</name>
        <uid>physiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>pedorthist</actor>
        <actors>pedorthists</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>An individual who is trained in the management and treatment of conditions of
            the foot, ankle, and lower extremities requiring fitting, fabricating, and adjusting of
            pedorthic devices.
        </description>
        <name>Pedorthist</name>
        <uid>pedorthist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Plastic Surgery Plastic Surgery Within the Head and Neck</actor>
        <actors>Plastic Surgery Plastic Surgery Within the Head and Necks</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A plastic surgeon with additional training in plastic and reconstructive
            procedures within the head, face, neck and associated structures, including cutaneous
            head and neck oncology and reconstruction, management of maxillofacial trauma, soft
            tissue repair and neural surgery. The field is diverse and involves a wide age range of
            patients, from the newborn to the aged. While both cosmetic and reconstructive surgery
            is practiced, there are many additional procedures which interface with them.
        </description>
        <name>Plastic Surgery Plastic Surgery Within the Head and Neck</name>
        <uid>plastic-surgery-plastic-surgery-within-the-head-and-neck</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Plastic Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Plastic Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in plastic and reconstructive surgery.</description>
        <name>Plastic Surgery</name>
        <uid>plastic-surgery-specialist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in physical therapy.</description>
        <name>Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Podiatric Foot Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Podiatric Foot Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in foot surgery.</description>
        <name>Foot Surgery</name>
        <uid>podiatry-foot-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Rehabilitation Counselor</actor>
        <actors>Rehabilitation Counselors</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>An individual trained and educated in a systematic process of assisting persons
            with physical, mental, developmental, cognitive, and emotional disabilities to achieve
            their personal, career, and independent living goals assessment and appraisal, diagnosis
            and treatment planning, career (vocational) counseling, individual and group counseling
            interventions for adjustments to the medical and psychosocial impact of disability, case
            management, program evaluation and research, job analysis and placement counseling, and
            consultation on rehabilitation resources and technology. Certification generally
            requires a Master's degree with specialized courses in rehabilitation processes and
            technology.
        </description>
        <name>Rehabilitation Counselor</name>
        <uid>rehabilitation-counselor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Diagnostic</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Diagnostics</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Included in the area of pulmonary diagnostics are the following; collection and
            analysis of physiological specimens, interpretation of physiological data,
            administration of tests of the cardiopulmonary system, and the conduct of both
            neurophysiological and sleep disorders studies.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Diagnostics</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-pulmonary-diagnostics</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Rehabilitation Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Rehabilitation Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in rehabilitation counceling and therapy.</description>
        <name>Rehabilitation Psychology</name>
        <uid>rehabilitation-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Diagnostic</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Diagnostics</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Included in the area of pulmonary diagnostics are the following; collection and
            analysis of physiological specimens, interpretation of physiological data,
            administration of tests of the cardiopulmonary system, and the conduct of both
            neurophysiological and sleep disorders studies.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Diagnostics</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-pulmonary-diagnostics</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered SNF/Subacute Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered SNF/Subacute Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Care of residents in a long-term care environment. Respiratory modalities
            delivered include those similar in the general care and critical care areas but provided
            to less critical patients.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered SNF/Subacute Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-snfsubacute-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Rheumatologist</actor>
        <actors>Rheumatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in joints, muscles, bones and tendons.</description>
        <name>Rheumatology</name>
        <uid>rheumatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Radiology Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Radiology Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Radiology</name>
        <uid>radiology-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Reconstructive Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Reconstructive Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in reconstructive surgery, including hip and knee.</description>
        <name>Adult Reconstructive orthopedic Surgery</name>
        <uid>reconstructive-orthopedist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified General Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified General Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>This level of care includes diagnostics testing, therapeutics, monitoring,
            rehabilitation of patients with disorders of the cardiopulmonary system, as well as,
            education of the patient and family in regard to those disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified General Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-general-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Educational</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Educationals</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The focus of patient and family education activities is to promote knowledge of
            disease process, medical therapy, and self help. Respiratory therapists are uniquely
            qualified to provide this service in regard to cardiopulmonary diseases and injury.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Educational</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-educational</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Geriatric Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Geriatric Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Care of older patients who have age and/or disease related decremental
            pulmonary changes. Diagnosis and treatment is very important for this group since
            chronic lung disease is the major cause of morbidity and mortality among them.
            Furthermore, as this segment of the population increases, life expectancy is being
            extended.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Geriatric Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-geriatric-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certifieds</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>A Certified Respiratory Therapist (CRT) is a an entry level therapist who has
            passed a standardized written examination administered by the National Board for
            Respiratory Care (NBRC). CRTs provide diagnostic testing, therapeutics, monitoring,
            rehabilitation, and education to patients with disorders of the cardiopulmonary system.
            They provide these respiratory care services in all health care facilities and in the
            home. A CRT is a graduate of an associate degree program approved by the Commission on
            Accreditation of Allied Health Educational Programs (CAAHEP) and where applicable, is
            licensed by the state and is practicing within the scope of the license.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Preventive Medical Toxicologist</actor>
        <actors>Preventive Medical Toxicologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in preventing illnesses related to drugs and chemicals.
        </description>
        <name>Preventive Medical Toxicology</name>
        <uid>preventive-medical-toxicologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Podiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Podiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in foot and ankle problems.</description>
        <name>Primary Podiatric Medicine</name>
        <uid>primary-podiatry-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Procedural Dermatologist</actor>
        <actors>Procedural Dermatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in skin related surgical operations.</description>
        <name>Procedural Dermatology</name>
        <uid>procedural-dermatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Behavioral Neurology &amp; Neuropsychiatry</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Behavioral Neurology &amp; Neuropsychiatries</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Behavioral Neurology &amp; Neuropsychiatry is a medical subspecialty involving
            the diagnosis and treatment of neurologically based behavioral issues.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Behavioral Neurology &amp; Neuropsychiatry</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-behavioral-neurology-neuropsychiatry</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Diagnostic Neuroimaging</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Diagnostic Neuroimagings</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A licensed physician, who has completed a residency program in Neurology, and
            who has additional training, experience, and competence in the standards of performance
            and interpretation of Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI / MRA) of the head, spine, and
            peripheral nerves, and Computed Tomography (CT) of the head and spine. Physicians are
            trained in the administration of contrast media and the recognition and treatment of
            adverse reactions to contrast media. Neuroimaging training encompasses thorough
            knowledge of clinical neurology, neurophysiology, neuroanatomy, neurochemistry,
            neuropharmacology, and dynamics of cerebrospinal fluid circulation. Physicians possess
            special expertise in the technical aspects and clinical applications of each of the
            modalities and techniques of neuroimaging.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Diagnostic Neuroimaging</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-diagnostic-neuroimaging</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Psychosomatic Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Psychosomatic Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Psychosomatic Medicine is subspecialty in the diagnosis and treatment of
            psychiatric disorders and symptoms in complex medically ill patients. This subspecialty
            includes treatment of patients with acute or chronic medical, neurological, obstetrical
            or surgical illness in which psychiatric illness is affecting their medical care and/or
            quality of life such as HIV infection, organ transplantation, heart disease, renal
            failure, cancer, stroke, traumatic brain injury, high-risk pregnancy and COPD, among
            others. Patients also may be those who have a psychiatric disorder that is the direct
            consequence of a primary medical condition, or a somatoform disorder or psychological
            factors affecting a general medical condition. Psychiatrists specializing in
            Psychosomatic Medicine provide consultation-liaison services in general medical
            hospitals, attend on medical psychiatry inpatient units, and provide collaborative care
            in primary care and other outpatient settings.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Psychosomatic Medicine</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-psychosomatic-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Critical Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Critical Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Respiratory emergencies are commonplace in the treatment of critical care
            patients. Included in the assessment measurements conducted by the respiratory therapist
            in the critical care settings are arterial blood gas puncture and analysis, intrarterial
            monitoring, bedside measurements of lung mechanics, hemodynamic monitoring, and inspired
            and expired gas measurements. This is coupled with the initiation and management of
            mechanical ventilation patients.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Critical Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-critical-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sports Medicine Orthopedist</actor>
        <actors>Sports Medicine Orthopedists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in surgery and treatment of sport related injuries.</description>
        <name>Orthopedic Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>sports-medicine-orthopedist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified SNF/Subacute Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified SNF/Subacute Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Care of residents in a long-term care environment. Respiratory modalities
            delivered include those similar in the general care and critical care areas but provided
            to less critical patients.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified SNF/Subacute Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-snfsubacute-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Critical Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Critical Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Respiratory emergencies are commonplace in the treatment of critical care
            patients. Included in the assessment measurements conducted by the respiratory therapist
            in the critical care settings are arterial blood gas puncture and analysis, intrarterial
            monitoring, bedside measurements of lung mechanics, hemodynamic monitoring, and inspired
            and expired gas measurements. This is coupled with the initiation and management of
            mechanical ventilation patients.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Critical Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-critical-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>School Counselor</actor>
        <actors>School Counselors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in school counseling.</description>
        <name>School Counseling</name>
        <uid>school-counselor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Ocularist</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Ocularists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Ocularist</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-ocularist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Acupuncturist</actor>
        <actors>Acupuncturists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in ancient alternative therapy via needles.</description>
        <name>Acupuncture</name>
        <uid>acupuncturist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Acute Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Acute Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in immediate care.</description>
        <name>Acute Care Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>acute-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Addiction Psychiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Addiction Psychiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alcohol, drug and substance problems.</description>
        <name>Addiction Psychiatry</name>
        <uid>addiction-psychiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in psychological counceling and therapy.</description>
        <name>Clinical Psychology</name>
        <uid>clinical-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Anaplastologist</actor>
        <actors>Anaplastologists</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>An anaplastologist is a professional who creates prostheses for the face and
            body. Patients treated include those missing anatomy due to cancer, traumatic injury, or
            birth differences. Generally, there are no state licensing requirements for
            anaplastologists. Certification specific to anaplastology is provided through the Board
            for Certified Clinical Anaplastology (BCCA) with a credential title of Certified
            Clinical Anaplastologist (CCA).
        </description>
        <name>Anaplastologist</name>
        <uid>anaplastologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Aerospace Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Aerospace Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in health and safety of airplane crewmembers and passangers.
        </description>
        <name>Aerospace Medicine</name>
        <uid>aerospace-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Anesthesiologist</actor>
        <actors>Anesthesiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in managing pain and anesthesia in surgeries.</description>
        <name>Anesthesiology</name>
        <uid>anesthesiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Cardiopulmonary Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Cardiopulmonary Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in heart and lung related physical therapy.</description>
        <name>Cardiopulmonary Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>cardiopulmonary-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Health Service Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Health Service Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in patients whose functioning is impaired.</description>
        <name>Health Service Psychology</name>
        <uid>health-service-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Developmental Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Developmental Therapists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>A Developmental Therapist is a person qualified by completion of an approved
            program in Developmental Therapy and where applicable credentialed by the state and
            practicing within the scope of the credential, or credentialed by completion of
            education experiences as approved by the state and practicing within the scope of that
            credential or, where state credentialing does not exist, certified by the Board of the
            Developmental Therapy Association. A developmental therapist evaluates children's global
            development in order to identify areas of developmental delay whether arising from
            physiological, neurological, or environmental factors, or a combination of factors; and
            designs, implements, and modifies therapeutic interventions for the child and the family
            to promote the child's acquisition of skills in a variety of developmental areas,
            including cognitive processes and social interaction in order to maximize functional
            independence and developmental homeostasis, and improve the quality of life at home and
            in the community; and provides consultation for the parents and other professionals
            working with the family on global development.
        </description>
        <name>Developmental Therapist</name>
        <uid>developmental-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Developmental Behavioral Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Developmental Behavioral Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in developmental difficulties and problematic behaviors in
            children.
        </description>
        <name>Developmental Behavioral Pediatrics</name>
        <uid>developmental-behavioral-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Forensic Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Forensic Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in psychology related criminal matters.</description>
        <name>Forensic Psychology</name>
        <uid>forensic-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Geriatric Psychiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Geriatric Psychiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnosis and treatment of mental disorders in the
            elderly.
        </description>
        <name>Geriatric Psychiatry</name>
        <uid>geriatric-psychiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Pharmacology</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Pharmacologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Clinical pharmacology encompasses the spectrum of activities related to the
            discovery, development, regulation, and utilization of safe and effective drugs.
        </description>
        <name>Clinical Pharmacology</name>
        <uid>clinical-pharmacology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Critical Care Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Critical Care Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the care of critically ill patients.</description>
        <name>Critical Care Medicine</name>
        <uid>critical-care-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hearing Aid Audiologist</actor>
        <actors>Hearing Aid Audiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in hearing and hearing aids.</description>
        <name>Audiology &amp; Hearing Aid Fitter</name>
        <uid>hearing-aid-audiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hospice Care and Palliative Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Hospice Care and Palliative Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in preventing and relieving suffering of dying patients.
        </description>
        <name>Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>hospice-care-palliative-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Independent Medical Examiner</actor>
        <actors>Independent Medical Examiners</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>A special evaluator not involved with the medical care of the individual
            examinee that impartially evaluates the care being provided by other practitioners to
            clarify clinical, disability, liability or other case issues.
        </description>
        <name>Independent Medical Examiner</name>
        <uid>independent-medical-examiner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Adolescent Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Adolescent Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An internist who specializes in adolescent medicine is a multi-disciplinary
            healthcare specialist trained in the unique physical, psychological and social
            characteristics of adolescents, their healthcare problems and needs.
        </description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Adolescent Medicine</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-adolescent-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Bariatric Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Bariatric Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Bariatric medicine is the medical treatment of obesity and its associated
            conditions. Bariatric medicine addresses the obese individual with a comprehensive
            program of diet, exercise and behavior modification, and when indicated, the
            prescription of appropriate medications as determined by the Bariatric physician.
            Bariatric physicians are licensed physicians who offer specialized programs in the
            medical treatment of obesity and its associated conditions.
        </description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Bariatric Medicine</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-bariatric-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Sports Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Sports Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An internist trained to be responsible for continuous care in the field of
            sports medicine, not only for the enhancement of health and fitness, but also for the
            prevention of injury and illness. A sports medicine physician must have knowledge and
            experience in the promotion of wellness and the prevention of injury. Knowledge about
            special areas of medicine such as exercise physiology, biomechanics, nutrition,
            psychology, physical rehabilitation, epidemiology, physical evaluation, injuries
            (treatment and prevention and referral practice) and the role of exercise in promoting a
            healthy lifestyle are essential to the practice of sports medicine. The sports medicine
            physician requires special education to provide the knowledge to improve the healthcare
            of the individual.
        </description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-sports-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internist</actor>
        <actors>Internists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in common illnesses and complex medical problems.</description>
        <name>Internal Medicine</name>
        <uid>internist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Pathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of tissue and bodily fluids.</description>
        <name>Clinical Pathology/Laboratory Medicine</name>
        <uid>laboratory-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Interventional Cardiologist</actor>
        <actors>Interventional Cardiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in heart imaging and diagnostics.</description>
        <name>Interventional Cardiology</name>
        <uid>interventional-cardiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Medical Genetics Molecular Genetic Pathology</actor>
        <actors>Medical Genetics Molecular Genetic Pathologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A board certified subspecialty, the molecular genetic pathologist is expert in
            the principles, theory and technologies of molecular biology and molecular genetics.
            This expertise is used to make or confirm diagnoses of Mendelian genetic disorders, of
            human development, infectious diseases and malignancies and to assess the natural
            history of those disorders. A molecular genetic pathologist provides information about
            gene structure, function and alteration, and applies laboratory techniques for
            diagnosis, treatment and prognosis for individuals with related disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Medical Genetics Molecular Genetic Pathology</name>
        <uid>medical-genetics-molecular-genetic-pathology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Nutritionist</actor>
        <actors>Nutritionists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternative food and nutrition therapies.</description>
        <name>Nutrition Medicine</name>
        <uid>nutritionist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Obstetrics &amp; Gynecology Female Pelvic Medicine and Reconstructive Surgery</actor>
        <actors>Obstetrics &amp; Gynecology Female Pelvic Medicine and Reconstructive Surgeries
        </actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A subspecialist in Female Pelvic Medicine and Reconstructive Surgery is a
            physician in Urology or Obstetrics and Gynecology who, by virtue of education and
            training, is prepared to provide consultation and comprehensive management of women with
            complex benign pelvic conditions, lower urinary tract disorders, and pelvic floor
            dysfunction. Comprehensive management includes those diagnostic and therapeutic
            procedures necessary for the total care of the patient with these conditions and
            complications resulting from them.
        </description>
        <name>Obstetrics &amp; Gynecology Female Pelvic Medicine and Reconstructive Surgery</name>
        <uid>obstetrics-gynecology-female-pelvic-medicine-and-reconstructive-surgery</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>OBGYN</actor>
        <actors>OBGYNS</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the care of the female reproductive system.</description>
        <name>Obstetrics &amp; Gynecology</name>
        <uid>obstetrics-gynecologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>An occupational therapist is a person who has graduated from an entry-level
            occupational therapy program accredited by the Accreditation Council for Occupational
            Therapy Education (ACOTE) or predecessor organizations, or approved by the World
            Federation of Occupational Therapists (WFOT), or an equivalent international
            occupational therapy education program; has successfully completed a period of
            supervised fieldwork experience required by the occupational therapy program; has passed
            a nationally recognized entry-level examination for occupational therapists, and
            fulfills state requirements for licensure, certification, or registration. An
            occupational therapist provides interventions based on evaluation and which emphasize
            the therapeutic use of everyday life activities (i.e., occupations) with individuals or
            groups for the purpose of facilitating participation in roles and situations and in
            home, school, workplace, community and other settings. Occupational therapy services are
            provided for the purpose of promoting health and wellness and are provided to those who
            have or are at risk for developing an illness, injury, disease, disorder, condition,
            impairment, disability, activity limitation, or participation restriction. Occupational
            therapists address the physical, cognitive, psychosocial, sensory, and other aspects of
            occupational performance in a variety of contexts to support engagement in everyday life
            activities that affect health, well-being, and quality of life.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Music Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Music Therapists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Music therapists use music interventions to assess clients' strengths and
            needs, develop goals, implement services, and evaluate and document progress for
            individuals of all ages. Music therapists facilitate changes in physical, cognitive,
            emotional, and/or psychosocial health.
        </description>
        <name>Music Therapist</name>
        <uid>music-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neuromusculoskeletal Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Neuromusculoskeletal Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in holistic physical therapy to treat illnesses.</description>
        <name>Neuromusculoskeletal Medicine &amp; OMM</name>
        <uid>neuromusculoskeletal-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neonatal Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Neonatal Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in premature and ill new borns as well as high-risk pregnancies.
        </description>
        <name>Neonatal, Critical Care Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>neonatal-critical-care-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neurosurgeon</actor>
        <actors>Neurosurgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in nervous system and brain surgery.</description>
        <name>Neurological Surgery</name>
        <uid>neurosurgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Nuclear Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Nuclear Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnosing and treating diseases with radioactive materials.
        </description>
        <name>Nuclear Medicine</name>
        <uid>nuclear-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Ergonomic</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Ergonomics</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Ergonomics</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-ergonomics</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Environmental Modification</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Environmental Modifications</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapy practitioners are experts at identifying the cause of
            difficulties in performance of activities of daily living and instrumental activities of
            daily living. Occupational therapy practitioners evaluate the client, their environment,
            and their occupational performance in that environment, as well as make recommendations
            for products to improve the fit between the client, place, and activity. Occupational
            therapists can evaluate both the skills of the client and the environmental features
            that support or limit the performance of meaningful or necessary activities, thereby
            enhancing health, safety and well-being. Based on this assessment, they recommend
            modification and intervention strategies that improve the fit between the person and his
            or her environment.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Environmental Modification</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-environmental-modification</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Orthopedic Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Orthopedic Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Orthopedics</name>
        <uid>orthopedic-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Otology Neurotologist</actor>
        <actors>Otology Neurotologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in ear and hearing problems.</description>
        <name>Otology &amp; Neurotology</name>
        <uid>otology-neurotologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Ophthalmologist</actor>
        <actors>Ophthalmologists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Specializes in vision, eye care, and eye surgery including Lasik.</description>
        <name>Ophthalmology</name>
        <uid>ophthalmologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Oncologist</actor>
        <actors>Oncologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnosis and treatment of cancer and tumors.</description>
        <name>Hematology &amp; Oncology</name>
        <uid>oncologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Diagnostic Ultrasound Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Diagnostic Ultrasound Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnostic ultrasound.</description>
        <name>Diagnostic Ultrasound</name>
        <uid>diagnostic-ultrasound-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Cardiothoracic Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Cardiothoracic Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in chest and heart surgery.</description>
        <name>Cardiothoracic Surgery</name>
        <uid>cardiothoracic-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Emergency Medicine Physician</actor>
        <actors>Emergency Medicine Physicians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An emergency medicine physician with special knowledge and skills to prevent
            and relieve the suffering experienced by patients with life-limiting illnesses. This
            specialist works with an interdisciplinary hospice or palliative care team to maximize
            quality of life while addressing physical, psychological, social and spiritual needs of
            both patient and family throughout the course of the disease, through the dying process,
            and beyond for the family. This specialist has expertise in the assessment of patients
            with advanced disease; the relief of distressing symptoms; the coordination of
            interdisciplinary patient and family-centered care in diverse venues; the use of
            specialized care systems including hospice; the management of the imminently dying
            patient; and legal and ethical decision making in end-of-life care.
        </description>
        <name>Emergency Medicine Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>emergency-medicine-hospice-and-palliative-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Cardiologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Cardiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children with heart problems.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Cardiology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-cardiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Environmental Preventive Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Environmental Preventive Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in environmental related preventive care.</description>
        <name>Environmental Preventive Medicine</name>
        <uid>environmental-preventive-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dietitian</actor>
        <actors>Dietitians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternative food and nutrition therapies.</description>
        <name>Dietitian, Registered</name>
        <uid>dietitian</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Mental Health Counselor</actor>
        <actors>Mental Health Counselors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in mental health service counseling.</description>
        <name>Mental Health Counseling</name>
        <uid>mental-health-counselor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Nephrologist</actor>
        <actors>Nephrologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in patients with kidney disorders.</description>
        <name>Nephrology</name>
        <uid>nephrologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Emergency Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Emergency Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in immediate decisions and actions related to children's health.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Emergency Medicine</name>
        <uid>emergency-medicine-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Preventive Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Preventive Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in preventive care and public health.</description>
        <name>Preventive Medicine</name>
        <uid>preventive-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Podiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Podiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in foot and ankle problems.</description>
        <name>Podiatry</name>
        <uid>podiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Gastroenterologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Gastroenterologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's digestive system.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Gastroenterology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-gastroenterologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the health of children from birth to young adulthood.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>pediatric-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Facial Plastic Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Facial Plastic Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in facial, plastic and reconstructive surgery.</description>
        <name>Otolaryngology/Facial Plastic Surgery</name>
        <uid>otolaryngology-facial-plastic-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Orthotist</actor>
        <actors>Orthotists</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>A health care professional who is specifically educated and trained to manage
            comprehensive orthotic patient care, including musculoskeletal and neuromuscular
            anomalies resulting from injuries or disease processes involving the lower extremity,
            upper extremity or spinal segment/s and positional deformation of the cranium.
            Orthotists assess specific patient needs, formulate an appropriate treatment plan,
            implement the treatment plan and provide follow-up care.
        </description>
        <name>Orthotist</name>
        <uid>orthotist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pastoral Counselor</actor>
        <actors>Pastoral Counselors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in behavioral health service counseling.</description>
        <name>Pastoral Counseling</name>
        <uid>pastoral-counselor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the health of children from birth to young adulthood.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatrics</name>
        <uid>pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Optometrist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Optometrists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's eye and visual problems.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Optometry</name>
        <uid>pediatric-optometrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Medical Toxicologist</actor>
        <actors>Medical Toxicologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in injury and illness from exposures to drugs and chemicals
        </description>
        <name>Medical Toxicology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-medical-toxicologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Addiction Medicine Anesthesiologist</actor>
        <actors>Addiction Medicine Anesthesiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnosis and treatment of addictions.</description>
        <name>Addiction Medicine</name>
        <uid>addiction-medicine-anesthesiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Allergy &amp; Immunology Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunology</actor>
        <actors>Allergy &amp; Immunology Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Allergy &amp; Immunology Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunology</name>
        <uid>allergy-immunology-clinical-laboratory-immunology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Adolescent Medicine Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Adolescent Medicine Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the health of children from 9 to 14 years old.</description>
        <name>Adolescent Medicine</name>
        <uid>adolescent-medicine-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Critical Care Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Critical Care Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the care of critically ill children.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Critical Care Medicine</name>
        <uid>critical-care-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Cytopathologist</actor>
        <actors>Cytopathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of human cells, including Pap test.
        </description>
        <name>Cytopathology</name>
        <uid>cytopathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dental Assistant</actor>
        <actors>Dental Assistants</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>An individual who may or may not have completed an accredited dental assisting
            education program and who aids the dentist in providing patient care services and
            performs other nonclinical duties in the dental office or other patient care facility.
            The scope of the patient care functions that may be legally delegated to the dental
            assistant varies based on the needs of the dentist the educational preparation of the
            dental assistant and state dental practice acts and regulations. Patient care services
            are provided under the supervision of a dentist. To avoid misleading the public, no
            occupational title other than dental assistant should be used to describe this dental
            auxiliary.
        </description>
        <name>Dental Assistant</name>
        <uid>dental-assistant</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dentist</actor>
        <actors>Dentists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>The science and art of preventing and controlling dental diseases and promoting
            dental health through organized community efforts. It is that form of dental practice
            that serves the community as a patient rather than the individual. It is concerned with
            the dental health education of the public, with applied dental research, and with the
            administration of group dental care programs as well as the prevention and control of
            dental diseases on a community basis.
        </description>
        <name>Dentist Dental Public Health</name>
        <uid>dentist-dental-public-health</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Anatomic Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Anatomic Pathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of tissue and bodily fluids.</description>
        <name>Anatomic Pathology</name>
        <uid>anatomic-pathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Art Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Art Therapists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>(1) An individual who uses art to achieve the therapeutic goals of symptom
            relief, emotional integration, and recovery from or adjustment to illness or disability.
            (2) An art therapist uses a form of treatment that enables patients with mental or
            physical disabilities to use art as a way of expressing and dealing with feelings and
            inner conflicts. (3) An individual who uses arts modalities and creative processes
            during intentional intervention in therapeutic, rehabilitative, community, or
            educational settings to foster health, communication, and expression; promote the
            integration of physical, emotional, cognitive, and social functioning; enhance
            self-awareness; and facilitate change.
        </description>
        <name>Art Therapist</name>
        <uid>art-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Counceling Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Counceling Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in psychological counceling.</description>
        <name>Counseling Psychology</name>
        <uid>counceling-pshychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Denturist</actor>
        <actors>Denturists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Definition to come.</description>
        <name>Denturist</name>
        <uid>denturist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Cognitive &amp; Behavioral Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Cognitive &amp; Behavioral Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in understanding and researching human behaviour.</description>
        <name>Cognitive &amp; Behavioral Psychology</name>
        <uid>cognitive-behavioral-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Child Psychiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Child Psychiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnosis and treatment of children's mental disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Child &amp; Adolescent Psychiatry</name>
        <uid>child-psychiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dentist Dentist Anesthesiologist</actor>
        <actors>Dentist Dentist Anesthesiologists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>A dentist who has successfully completed an accredited postdoctoral
            anesthesiology residency training program for dentists of two or more years duration, in
            accord with Commission on Dental Accreditation's Standards for Dental Anesthesiology
            Residency Programs, and/or meets the eligibility requirements for examination by the
            American Dental Board of Anesthesiology.
        </description>
        <name>Dentist Dentist Anesthesiologist</name>
        <uid>dentist-dentist-anesthesiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dermatopathologist</actor>
        <actors>Dermatopathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnoses and monitoring skin diseases.</description>
        <name>Dermatopathology</name>
        <uid>dermatopathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Diagnostic Neuroimaging Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Diagnostic Neuroimaging Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in computer imaging including MRI and CT scans.</description>
        <name>Diagnostic Neuroimaging</name>
        <uid>diagnostic-neuroimaging-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Family Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in your and your family's health.</description>
        <name>Family Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>family-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hospice and Palliative Medicine Anesthesiologist</actor>
        <actors>Hospice and Palliative Medicine Anesthesiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in relieving the suffering of dying patients.</description>
        <name>Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>hospice-palliative-medicine-anesthesiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hospice and Palliative Physiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Hospice and Palliative Physiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in reliving the suffering of dying patients.</description>
        <name>Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>hospice-palliative-physiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hospitalist</actor>
        <actors>Hospitalists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in general medical care of hospitalized patients.</description>
        <name>Hospitalist</name>
        <uid>hospitalist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Head &amp; Neck Plastic Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Head &amp; Neck Plastic Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in head and neck plastic and reconstructive surgery.</description>
        <name>Plastic Surgery within the Head &amp; Neck</name>
        <uid>head-neck-plastic-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>General Practitioner</actor>
        <actors>General Practitioners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes and treats your total health.</description>
        <name>General Practice</name>
        <uid>general-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>General Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>General Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in complex surgical operations.</description>
        <name>Surgery</name>
        <uid>general-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Gynecologist</actor>
        <actors>Gynecologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the care of the female reproductive system.</description>
        <name>Gynecology</name>
        <uid>gynecologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Internal Medicine</name>
        <uid>internist-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Massage Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Massage Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternative therapy of muscles and tissue.</description>
        <name>Massage Therapy</name>
        <uid>massage-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neuroradiologist</actor>
        <actors>Neuroradiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in imaging of the brain, spine and spinal cord.</description>
        <name>Neuroradiology</name>
        <uid>neuroradiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Nuclear Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Nuclear Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in imaging with radiologic substances.</description>
        <name>Nuclear Radiology</name>
        <uid>nuclear-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Human Factor</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Human Factors</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Human Factors</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-human-factors</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Allergy &amp; Immunology</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Allergy &amp; Immunologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An internist doctor of osteopathy that specializes in the treatment of allergy
            and immunologic disorders. A doctor of osteopathy that is board eligible/certified by
            the American Osteopathic Board of Internal Medicine can obtain a Certificate of Special
            Qualifications in the field of Allergy &amp; Immunology.
        </description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Allergy &amp; Immunology</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-allergy-immunology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI)</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI)S</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Definition to come.</description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI)</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-magnetic-resonance-imaging-mri</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Podiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Podiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description />
        <name>Podiatrist General Practice</name>
        <uid>podiatrist-general-practice</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Physical Rehabilitation</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Physical Rehabilitations</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapists are experts at helping people lead as independent a
            life as possible. Occupational therapists bring an understanding of the physical and
            psychological implications of illness and injury and their effects on peoples' ability
            to perform the tasks of daily living. Occupational therapists provide interventions that
            can aide a person in completing ADL and IADL tasks, such as dressing, bathing, preparing
            meals, and driving. They also may fabricate custom orthotics to improve function,
            evaluate the environment for safety hazards and recommend adaptations to remove those
            hazards, help a person compensate for cognitive changes, and build a persons' physical
            endurance and strength. Occupational therapists' knowledge of adapting tasks and
            modifying the environment to compensate for functional limitations is used to increase
            the involvement of clients and to promote safety and success.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Physical Rehabilitation</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-physical-rehabilitation</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapy Assistant Environmental Modification</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapy Assistant Environmental Modifications</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapy assistants provide environmental modifications under the
            supervision of an occupational therapist. OTAs develop and implement an individualized
            occupational therapy environmental modification plan that reflects the relevant contexts
            of the client and relevant others and maximizes current and future occupational
            performance, safety, and participation of the client. Clients receive environmental
            modification recommendations and interventions that enable them to meet occupational
            performance and participation goals and that have adequate flexibility to accommodate
            for their future needs.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapy Assistant Environmental Modification</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapy-assistant-environmental-modification</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Medical Oncologist</actor>
        <actors>Medical Oncologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnosis and treatment of cancer and tumors.</description>
        <name>Medical Oncology</name>
        <uid>medical-oncologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>General Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>General Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in your and your family's health.</description>
        <name>Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Optometrist</actor>
        <actors>Optometrists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Specializes in vision and prescribing glasses and contact lenses.</description>
        <name>Optometry</name>
        <uid>optometrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Urology Female Pelvic Medicine and Reconstructive Surgery</actor>
        <actors>Urology Female Pelvic Medicine and Reconstructive Surgeries</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A subspecialist in Female Pelvic Medicine and Reconstructive Surgery is a
            physician in Urology or Obstetrics and Gynecology who, by virtue of education and
            training, is prepared to provide consultation and comprehensive management of women with
            complex benign pelvic conditions, lower urinary tract disorders, and pelvic floor
            dysfunction. Comprehensive management includes those diagnostic and therapeutic
            procedures necessary for the total care of the patient with these conditions and
            complications resulting from them.
        </description>
        <name>Urology Female Pelvic Medicine and Reconstructive Surgery</name>
        <uid>urology-female-pelvic-medicine-and-reconstructive-surgery</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Oral Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Oral Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in X-rays of the mouth, jaw and face.</description>
        <name>Oral and Maxillofacial Radiology</name>
        <uid>oral-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Orthodontist</actor>
        <actors>Orthodontists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in the correction of teeth and surrounding structures.
        </description>
        <name>Orthodontics</name>
        <uid>orthodontist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Diagnostic Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Diagnostic Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in imaging via X-rays and ultrasound.</description>
        <name>Diagnostic Radiology</name>
        <uid>diagnostic-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Endocrinologist</actor>
        <actors>Endocrinologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diabetes, thyroid and other disorders affected by hormones.
        </description>
        <name>Endocrinology, Diabetes &amp; Metabolism</name>
        <uid>endocrinologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Endotontist</actor>
        <actors>Endotontists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in root canal and other similar issues.</description>
        <name>Endodontics</name>
        <uid>endotontist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Medicine Geriatric Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Family Medicine Geriatric Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A family medicine physician with special knowledge of the aging process and
            special skills in the diagnostic, therapeutic, preventive and rehabilitative aspects of
            illness in the elderly. This specialist cares for geriatric patients in the patient's
            home, the office, long-term care settings such as nursing homes, and the hospital.
        </description>
        <name>Family Medicine Geriatric Medicine</name>
        <uid>family-medicine-geriatric-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Medicine Bariatric Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Family Medicine Bariatric Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Bariatric medicine is the medical treatment of obesity and its associated
            conditions. Bariatric medicine addresses the obese individual with a comprehensive
            program of diet, exercise and behavior modification, and when indicated, the
            prescription of appropriate medications as determined by the Bariatric physician.
            Bariatric physicians are licensed physicians who offer specialized programs in the
            medical treatment of obesity and its associated conditions.
        </description>
        <name>Family Medicine Bariatric Medicine</name>
        <uid>family-medicine-bariatric-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>In Vivo &amp; In Vitro Nuclear Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>In Vivo &amp; In Vitro Nuclear Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnosing and treating diseases with radioactive materials.
        </description>
        <name>In Vivo &amp; In Vitro Nuclear Medicine</name>
        <uid>vivo-vitro-nuclear-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Interventional Pain Management Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Interventional Pain Management Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in pain management and prevention.</description>
        <name>Interventional Pain Medicine</name>
        <uid>interventional-pain-management-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Mastectomy Fitter</actor>
        <actors>Mastectomy Fitters</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>An individual trained in the fitting and adjusting of breast prostheses and
            management of post-mastectomy prostheses services.
        </description>
        <name>Mastectomy Fitter</name>
        <uid>mastectomy-fitter</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Maternal &amp; Fetal OBGYN</actor>
        <actors>Maternal &amp; Fetal OBGYNS</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in high-risk pregnancies and pregnancy complications.</description>
        <name>Maternal &amp; Fetal Medicine</name>
        <uid>maternal-fetal-medicine-obgyn</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Hematology &amp; Oncologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Hematology &amp; Oncologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in disorders that involve blood, spleen and lymph as well as cancer
            or other tumors.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Hematology &amp; Oncology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-oncologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Pathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of tissue and bodily fluids in children.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Pathology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-pathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Transplant Hepatologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Transplant Hepatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's liver transplants.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Transplant Hepatology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-transplant-hepatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Bariatric Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Bariatric Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Bariatric medicine is the medical treatment of obesity and its associated
            conditions. Bariatric medicine addresses the obese individual with a comprehensive
            program of diet, exercise and behavior modification, and when indicated, the
            prescription of appropriate medications as determined by the Bariatric physician.
            Bariatric physicians are licensed physicians who offer specialized programs in the
            medical treatment of obesity and its associated conditions.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Bariatric Medicine</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-bariatric-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Hospice and Palliative Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Hospice and Palliative Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A psychiatrist or neurologist with special knowledge and skills to prevent and
            relieve the suffering experienced by patients with life-limiting illnesses. This
            specialist works with an interdisciplinary hospice or palliative care team to maximize
            quality of life while addressing physical, psychological, social and spiritual needs of
            both patient and family throughout the course of the disease, through the dying process,
            and beyond for the family. This specialist has expertise in the assessment of patients
            with advanced disease; the relief of distressing symptoms; the coordination of
            interdisciplinary patient and family-centered care in diverse venues; the use of
            specialized care systems including hospice; the management of the imminently dying
            patient; and legal and ethical decision making in end-of-life care.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-hospice-and-palliative-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Podiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Podiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Podiatrist Public Medicine</name>
        <uid>podiatrist-public-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Preventive Sports Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Preventive Sports Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in sport related preventive care.</description>
        <name>Preventive Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>preventive-sports-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neurologist</actor>
        <actors>Neurologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the brain and nervous system.</description>
        <name>Neurology</name>
        <uid>neurologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neurodevelopmental Disability Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Neurodevelopmental Disability Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in developmental delays or learning disorders in children.
        </description>
        <name>Neurodevelopmental Disability</name>
        <uid>neurodevelopmental-disability-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Otolaryngic Allergist</actor>
        <actors>Otolaryngic Allergists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in ear, nose and throat allergies.</description>
        <name>Otolaryngic Allergy</name>
        <uid>otolaryngic-allergist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neurology Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Neurology Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in nervous system physical therapy.</description>
        <name>Neurology Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>neurology-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Nephrologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Nephrologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's kidney disorders.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Nephrology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-nephrologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Neurologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Neurologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's brain and nervous system.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Neurology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-neurologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Periodontist</actor>
        <actors>Periodontists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in gums and bones that support your teeth.</description>
        <name>Periodontics</name>
        <uid>periodontist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Plastic Surgery Surgery of the Hand</actor>
        <actors>Plastic Surgery Surgery of the Hands</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A plastic surgeon with additional training in the investigation, preservation,
            and restoration by medical, surgical and rehabilitative means of all structures of the
            upper extremity directly affecting the form and function of the hand and wrist.
        </description>
        <name>Plastic Surgery Surgery of the Hand</name>
        <uid>plastic-surgery-surgery-of-the-hand</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychoanalyst</actor>
        <actors>Psychoanalysts</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in psychoanalysis techniques developed by Sigmund Freud.
        </description>
        <name>Psychoanalysis</name>
        <uid>psychoanalyst</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in psychological counceling and therapy.</description>
        <name>Psychology</name>
        <uid>psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Patient Transport</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Patient Transports</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Transport respiratory therapist provide patient assessment, initiation of
            treatment modalities and continued monitoring of patient status of the critically ill
            and injured patients with special attention to advanced airway and ventilator
            management. The transport respiratory therapist knowledge and experience with complex
            neonatal, pediatric and adult patient care issues provides them with an expertise to
            assist with any patient care issue in a variety of transport modes.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Patient Transport</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-patient-transport</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Rehabilitation Practitioner</actor>
        <actors>Rehabilitation Practitioners</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>A health care practitioner who trains or retrains individuals disabled by
            disease or injury to help them attain their maximum functional capacity.
        </description>
        <name>Rehabilitation Practitioner</name>
        <uid>rehabilitation-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Recreation Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Recreation Therapists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>A recreation therapist uses recreational activities for intervention in some
            physical, social or emotional behavior to bring about a desired change in that behavior
            and promote the growth and development of the patient.
        </description>
        <name>Recreation Therapist</name>
        <uid>recreation-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Radiation Oncologist</actor>
        <actors>Radiation Oncologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in radiation treatment of cancer and tumors.</description>
        <name>Radiation Oncology</name>
        <uid>radiation-oncologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Rehabilitation Counselor Orientation and Mobility Training Provider</actor>
        <actors>Rehabilitation Counselor Orientation and Mobility Training Providers</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Orientation and Mobility (O&amp;M) specialists teach children and adults who
            have visual impairments the specific orientation skills used to find one's way in the
            environment and the mobility skills needed to travel safely and efficiently at home,
            school, work, and in the community. Instruction is usually provided one-on-one and can
            include skills such as how to use a long cane, the operation of low vision devices and
            electronic travel aids when appropriate, how to orient oneself to new environments,
            navigate public transportation systems, how to cross streets safely, and traveling by
            using hearing, remaining vision, and other senses. In addition, O&amp;M Specialists help
            children to develop fundamental skills such as fine and gross motor skills, concept
            development and problem solving skills. Adult clients can also benefit from an O&amp;M
            specialist evaluating their current use of travel-related skills, discussing their
            future goals, and helping them select a program of instruction that will allow them to
            reach their greatest travel potential.
        </description>
        <name>Rehabilitation Counselor Orientation and Mobility Training Provider</name>
        <uid>rehabilitation-counselor-orientation-and-mobility-training-provider</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Contact Lens Fitter</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Contact Lens Fitters</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>An optician or other ancillary support staff person who, where authorized by
            state law and trained or certified to do so, may fit or dispense contact lenses to a
            patient based on the prescription of an optometrist or medical physician.
        </description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Contact Lens Fitter</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-contact-lens-fitter</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Ophthalmic Assistant</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Ophthalmic Assistants</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Ophthalmic Assistant</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-ophthalmic-assistant</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Optometric Assistant</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Optometric Assistants</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Optometric Assistant</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-optometric-assistant</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>School Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>School Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in counceling and therapy in schools.</description>
        <name>School Psychology</name>
        <uid>school-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Specialist/Technologist Athletic Trainer</actor>
        <actors>Specialist/Technologist Athletic Trainers</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Athletic trainers are allied health care professionals who work in consultation
            with or under the direction of physicians, and specialize in the prevention, assessment,
            treatment and rehabilitation of injuries and illnesses. Currently, the entry-level
            employment requirements are a bachelor's degree with a major in athletic training from
            an accredited university or college. A majority of athletic trainers hold advanced
            degrees. National board certification is generally required as a condition of state
            licensure and employment. Most states regulate athletic trainers, and they practice
            within the scope of that license or regulation. Clinical practice includes emergency
            care, rehabilitation, reconditioning, therapeutic exercise, wellness programs, exercise
            physiology, kinesiology, biomechanics, nutrition, psychology and health care
            administration.
        </description>
        <name>Specialist/Technologist Athletic Trainer</name>
        <uid>specialisttechnologist-athletic-trainer</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Rehabilitation</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Rehabilitations</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The respiratory therapist can assist the chronic pulmonary patient in returning
            to an optimal role in society by providing an effective program. It includes
            bronchopulmonary drainage, exercise therapy, and patient education.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Rehabilitation</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-pulmonary-rehabilitation</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Surgery Surgical Critical Care</actor>
        <actors>Surgery Surgical Critical Cares</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A surgeon with expertise in the management of the critically ill and
            postoperative patient, particularly the trauma victim, who specializes in critical care
            medicine diagnoses, treats and supports patients with multiple organ dysfunction. This
            specialist may have administrative responsibilities for intensive care units and may
            also facilitate and coordinate patient care among the primary physician, the critical
            care staff and other specialists.
        </description>
        <name>Surgery Surgical Critical Care</name>
        <uid>surgery-surgical-critical-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Surgery Trauma Surgery</actor>
        <actors>Surgery Trauma Surgeries</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Trauma surgery is a recognized subspecialty of general surgery. Trauma surgeons
            are physicians who have completed a five-year general surgery residency and usually
            continue with a one to two year fellowship in trauma and/or surgical critical care,
            typically leading to additional board certification in surgical critical care. There is
            no trauma surgery board certification at this point. To obtain board certification in
            surgical critical care, a fellowship in surgical critical care or anesthesiology
            critical care must be completed during or after general surgery residency.
        </description>
        <name>Surgery Trauma Surgery</name>
        <uid>surgery-trauma-surgery</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Surgical Oncologist</actor>
        <actors>Surgical Oncologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the branch of surgery which focuses on the surgical management
            of cancer.
        </description>
        <name>Surgical Oncology</name>
        <uid>surgical-oncologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Ophthalmic</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Ophthalmics</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Ophthalmic</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-ophthalmic</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered General Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered General Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>This level of care includes diagnostics testing, therapeutics, monitoring,
            rehabilitation of patients with disorders of the cardiopulmonary system, as well as,
            education of the patient and family in regard to those disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered General Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-general-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Patient Transport</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Patient Transports</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Transport respiratory therapist provide patient assessment, initiation of
            treatment modalities and continued monitoring of patient status of the critically ill
            and injured patients with special attention to advanced airway and ventilator
            management. The transport respiratory therapist knowledge and experience with complex
            neonatal, pediatric and adult patient care issues provides them with an expertise to
            assist with any patient care issue in a variety of transport modes.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Patient Transport</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-patient-transport</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Palliative/Hospice</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Palliative/Hospices</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>A coordinated plan of care to help dying patients and their families handle the
            burden of terminal care. Effective secretion management and relief of dyspnea are
            paramount in caring for patients with end-stage pulmonary disease.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Palliative/Hospice</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-palliativehospice</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sports Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Sports Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>sports-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Specialist/Technologist</actor>
        <actors>Specialist/Technologists</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>General classification identifying individuals who are trained on a specific
            piece of equipment or technical procedure.
        </description>
        <name>Specialist/Technologist</name>
        <uid>specialisttechnologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Educational</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Educationals</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The focus of patient and family education activities is to promote knowledge of
            disease process, medical therapy, and self help. Respiratory therapists are uniquely
            qualified to provide this service in regard to cardiopulmonary diseases and injury.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Educational</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-educational</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Emergency Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Emergency Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The immediate availability of diagnostic and therapeutic cardiopulmonary
            services in the assessment and management of trauma victims, patients requiring airway
            management and others requiring emergency care.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Emergency Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-emergency-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Spine Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Spine Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in spine surgery and treatment.</description>
        <name>Orthopedic Surgery of the Spine</name>
        <uid>spine-orthopedist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Home Health</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Home Healths</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Home care fosters individual responsibility for self-management of chronic
            respiratory conditions. It includes individualized assessment based plans of care
            service developed to promote safe, proper, and sustained use of prescribed respiratory
            therapy medications, equipment, and techniques in the home.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Home Health</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-home-health</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Contact Len</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Contact Lens</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>An optician or other ancillary support staff person who, where authorized by
            state law and trained or certified to do so, may fit or dispense contact lenses to a
            patient based on the prescription of an optometrist or medical physician.
        </description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Contact Lens</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-contact-lens</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Trauma Orthopedist</actor>
        <actors>Trauma Orthopedists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in acute orthopedic injuries, including hip treatments.
        </description>
        <name>Orthopedic Trauma</name>
        <uid>trauma-orthopedist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Undersea and Hyperbaric Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Undersea and Hyperbaric Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diving related illnesses.</description>
        <name>Undersea and Hyperbaric Medicine</name>
        <uid>undersea-hyperbaric-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Optician</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Opticians</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Optician</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-optician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Optometric Technician</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Optometric Technicians</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Optometric Technician</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-optometric-technician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Transplant Surgery</actor>
        <actors>Transplant Surgeries</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Definition to come.</description>
        <name>Transplant Surgery</name>
        <uid>transplant-surgery</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Addiction Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Addiction Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specialzes in helping patients with physical and mental addictions.
        </description>
        <name>Addiction Psychology</name>
        <uid>addiction-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Allergist</actor>
        <actors>Allergists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in treatment of allergies and the immune system.</description>
        <name>Allergy &amp; Immunology</name>
        <uid>allergist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Corneal and Contact Management Optometrist</actor>
        <actors>Corneal and Contact Management Optometrists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Specializes in contact lenses.</description>
        <name>Corneal and Contact Management</name>
        <uid>corneal-contact-management-optometrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Colorectal Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Colorectal Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in colon and rectal surgery.</description>
        <name>Colon &amp; Rectal Surgery</name>
        <uid>colorectal-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Critical Care Anesthesiologist</actor>
        <actors>Critical Care Anesthesiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in managing anesthesia in critical surgeries.</description>
        <name>Critical Care Medicine</name>
        <uid>critical-care-anesthesiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Counselor</actor>
        <actors>Counselors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in behavioral health service counseling.</description>
        <name>Counseling</name>
        <uid>counselor-specialist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dental Hygienist</actor>
        <actors>Dental Hygienists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>An individual who has completed an accredited dental hygiene education program,
            and an individual who has been licensed by a state board of dental examiners to provide
            preventive care services under the supervision of a dentist. Functions that may be
            legally delegated to the dental hygienist vary based on the needs of the dentist, the
            educational preparation of the dental hygienist and state dental practice acts and
            regulations, but always include, at a minimum, scaling and polishing the teeth. To avoid
            misleading the public, no occupational title other than dental hygienist should be used
            to describe this dental auxiliary.
        </description>
        <name>Dental Hygienist</name>
        <uid>dental-hygienist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Health Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Health Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in counceling of patients with physical health problems.
        </description>
        <name>Health Psychology</name>
        <uid>health-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Human Factors Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Human Factors Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in physical therapy.</description>
        <name>Human Factor Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>human-factor-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Geneticist</actor>
        <actors>Geneticists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnoses of and counselling for genetic disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Medical Genetics, Ph.D. Medical Genetics</name>
        <uid>geneticist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Geriatric Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Geriatric Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in physical therapy for the elderly.</description>
        <name>Geriatrics Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>geriatric-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hand Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Hand Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in physical therapy of the hands.</description>
        <name>Hand Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>hand-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Foot and Ankle Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Foot and Ankle Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in foot and ankle surgery.</description>
        <name>Foot and Ankle Surgery</name>
        <uid>foot-ankle-orthopedist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Family Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in family counceling and therapy.</description>
        <name>Family Psychology</name>
        <uid>family-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Gastroenterologist</actor>
        <actors>Gastroenterologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the digestive system.</description>
        <name>Gastroenterology</name>
        <uid>gastroenterologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Practitioner</actor>
        <actors>Family Practitioners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in your and your family's total health.</description>
        <name>Family Medicine</name>
        <uid>family-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Feeding, Eating &amp; Swallowing</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Feeding, Eating &amp; Swallowings</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapists provide interventions to clients of all ages with
            feeding, eating and swallowing difficulties. Occupational therapists provide
            comprehensive rehabilitative, habilitative, and palliative dysphagia care, which
            includes collaborating with clients to provide individualized compensatory swallowing
            strategies, modified diet textures, adapted mealtime environments, enhanced feeding
            skills, preparatory exercises and positioning to clients, reinforcement of mealtime
            strategies to enhance and improve swallowing skills, and training to caregivers to
            enhance eating and feeding performance. Occupational therapists provide screening and
            in-depth clinical assessment which may include instrumental dysphagia assessments
            including videofluroscopy.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Feeding, Eating &amp; Swallowing</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-feeding-eating-swallowing</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Gerontology</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Gerontologies</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapists work with older adults in virtually every setting:
            assisted living, wellness programs, hospitals, nursing homes, senior centers, clinics
            and in the home. Occupational therapists bring an understanding of the importance of
            participation and occupation for overall well-being to those who are experiencing
            disabling conditions related to aging. The primary overarching goal of occupational
            therapy services with this population is to maximize independence and participation,
            thereby enabling an older person to continue to live successfully in his or her chosen
            environment. Occupational therapists can help older adults by developing strategies to
            help or maintain safety and well-being, to assist with life transitions, and to
            compensate for challenges they experience in activities of daily living, instrumental
            activities of daily living, leisure participation, social participation, and productive
            activities.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Gerontology</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-gerontology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neuromuscular Physiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Neuromuscular Physiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in neuromuscular medicine.</description>
        <name>Neuromuscular Medicine</name>
        <uid>neuromuscular-physiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Hand</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Hands</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Hand</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-hand</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hospice and Palliative Medicine Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Hospice and Palliative Medicine Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in relieving the suffering of dying patients.</description>
        <name>Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>hospice-palliative-medicine-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Immunopathologist</actor>
        <actors>Immunopathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnosis of immunologic diseases.</description>
        <name>Immunopathology</name>
        <uid>immunopathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Neurorehabilitation</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Neurorehabilitations</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Neurorehabilitation</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-neurorehabilitation</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Oral Medicinist</actor>
        <actors>Oral Medicinists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>A dentist with advanced training specializing in the recognition and treatment
            of oral conditions resulting from the interrelationship between oral disease and
            systemic health. The Oral Medicinist manages clinical and non-surgical treatment of
            non-dental pathologies affecting the oral and maxillofacial region, such as cancer,
            organ transplants, and acute and chronic pain. Activities include provision of
            interdisciplinary patient care in collaboration with medical specialists and other
            dentists in hospitals and outpatient medical clinics in the management of patients with
            complex medical conditions requiring multidisciplinary healthcare intervention.
        </description>
        <name>Oral Medicinist</name>
        <uid>oral-medicinist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Oral Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Oral Surgeons</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in surgical operations of the mouth, jaw and face.</description>
        <name>Oral &amp; Maxillofacial Surgery</name>
        <uid>oral-maxillofacial-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Pathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of tissue and bodily fluids.</description>
        <name>Pathology</name>
        <uid>pathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Sleep Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Sleep Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A Psychiatrist or Neurologist who practices Sleep Medicine is certified in the
            subspecialty of sleep medicine and specializes in the clinical assessment, physiologic
            testing, diagnosis, management and prevention of sleep and circadian rhythm disorders.
            Sleep specialists treat patients of any age and use multidisciplinary approaches.
            Disorders managed by sleep specialists include, but are not limited to, sleep related
            breathing disorders, insomnia, hypersomnias, circadian rhythm sleep disorders,
            parasomnias and sleep related movement disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Sleep Medicine</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-sleep-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Vascular Neurology</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Vascular Neurologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Vascular Neurology is a subspecialty in the evaluation, prevention, treatment
            and recovery from vascular diseases of the nervous system. This subspecialty includes
            the diagnosis and treatment of vascular events of arterial or venous origin from a large
            number of causes that affect the brain or spinal cord such as ischemic stroke,
            intracranial hemorrhage, spinal cord ischemia and spinal cord hemorrhage.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Vascular Neurology</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-vascular-neurology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Medicine Adolescent Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Family Medicine Adolescent Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A family medicine physician with multidisciplinary training in the unique
            physical, psychological and social characteristics of adolescents and their health care
            problems and needs.
        </description>
        <name>Family Medicine Adolescent Medicine</name>
        <uid>family-medicine-adolescent-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Cardiologist</actor>
        <actors>Cardiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in heart problems.</description>
        <name>Cardiovascular Disease</name>
        <uid>cardiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Cytogeneticist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Cytogeneticists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory diagnostics of genes.</description>
        <name>Clinical Cytogenetic</name>
        <uid>clinical-cytogeneticist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Electrophysiology Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Electrophysiology Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in wound management and physical therapy.</description>
        <name>Clinical Electrophysiology</name>
        <uid>electrophysiology-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Molecular Geneticist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Molecular Geneticists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in molecular diagnostics of genetic disorders.</description>
        <name>Clinical Molecular Genetics</name>
        <uid>clinical-molecular-geneticist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Exercise Physiologist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Exercise Physiologists</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>A Clinical Exercise Physiologist is a health care professional who is trained
            to work with patients with chronic disease where exercise training has been shown to be
            of therapeutic benefit, including but not limited to cardiovascular and pulmonary
            disease, and metabolic disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Clinical Exercise Physiologist</name>
        <uid>clinical-exercise-physiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Emergency Medicine Pediatric Emergency Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Emergency Medicine Pediatric Emergency Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Pediatric Emergency Medicine is a clinical subspecialty that focuses on the
            care of the acutely ill or injured child in the setting of an emergency department.
        </description>
        <name>Emergency Medicine Pediatric Emergency Medicine</name>
        <uid>emergency-medicine-pediatric-emergency-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Emergency Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Emergency Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in immediate emergency care.</description>
        <name>Emergency Medicine</name>
        <uid>emergency-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Ergonomic Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Ergonomic Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in ergonomics and physical therapy.</description>
        <name>Ergonomic Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>ergonomic-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pain Medicine Physiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Pain Medicine Physiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in treating patients with cronic or acute pain.</description>
        <name>Pain Medicine</name>
        <uid>pain-medicine-physiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Allergist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Allergists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in treatment of allergies and the immune system in children.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Allergy</name>
        <uid>pediatric-allergist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Orthopedic Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Orthopedic Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in surgery of musculoskeletal problems in children.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Orthopedic Surgery</name>
        <uid>pediatric-orhopedic-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neurology Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Neurology Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Neurology</name>
        <uid>neurology-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pain Medicine Anesthesiologist</actor>
        <actors>Pain Medicine Anesthesiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in managing acute and chronic pain.</description>
        <name>Pain Medicine</name>
        <uid>pain-medicine-anesthesiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Ear, Nose and Throat Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Ear, Nose and Throat Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's ear, nose and throat problems.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Otolaryngology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-ear-nose-throat-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Anesthesiologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Anesthesiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in managing pain and anesthesia in surgeries of children.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Anesthesiology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-anesthesiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pathology Clinical Informatic</actor>
        <actors>Pathology Clinical Informatics</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Physicians who practice Clinical Informatics collaborate with other health care
            and information technology professionals to analyze, design, implement and evaluate
            information and communication systems that enhance individual and population health
            outcomes, improve patient care, and strengthen the clinician-patient relationship.
            Clinical Informaticians use their knowledge of patient care combined with their
            understanding of informatics concepts, methods, and tools to: assess information and
            knowledge needs of health care professionals and patients; characterize, evaluate, and
            refine clinical processes; develop, implement, and refine clinical decision support
            systems; and lead or participate in the procurement, customization, development,
            implementation, management, evaluation, and continuous improvement of clinical
            information systems.
        </description>
        <name>Pathology Clinical Informatics</name>
        <uid>pathology-clinical-informatics</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Endocrinologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Endocrinologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diabetes, thyroid, growth and hormonal disorders in children.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Endocrinology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-endocrinologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Rehabilitation Physiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Rehabilitation Physiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in treating children with physical disabilities.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Rehabilitation Medicine</name>
        <uid>pediatric-rehabilitation-physiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatrics Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunology</actor>
        <actors>Pediatrics Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A pediatrician who specializes in clinical and laboratory immunology disease
            management.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatrics Clinical &amp; Laboratory Immunology</name>
        <uid>pediatrics-clinical-laboratory-immunology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Podiatric Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Podiatric Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in foot and ankle surgery.</description>
        <name>Foot &amp; Ankle Surgery</name>
        <uid>podiatry-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Prosthodontist</actor>
        <actors>Prosthodontists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in restoration and replacement of teeth.</description>
        <name>Prosthodontics</name>
        <uid>prosthodontist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Radiological Physicist</actor>
        <actors>Radiological Physicists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnostics via roentgen and gamma rays.</description>
        <name>Radiological Physics</name>
        <uid>radiological-physicist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Rehabilitation Counselor Assistive Technology Supplier</actor>
        <actors>Rehabilitation Counselor Assistive Technology Suppliers</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Rehabilitation Counselor Assistive Technology Supplier</name>
        <uid>rehabilitation-counselor-assistive-technology-supplier</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Neurodevelopmental Disability</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Neurodevelopmental Disabilities</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A pediatrician or neurologist who specializes in the diagnosis and management
            of chronic conditions that affect the developing and mature nervous system such as
            cerebral palsy, mental retardation and chronic behavioral syndromes, or neurologic
            conditions.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Neurodevelopmental Disabilities</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-neurodevelopmental-disabilities</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Home Health</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Home Healths</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Home care fosters individual responsibility for self-management of chronic
            respiratory conditions. It includes individualized assessment based plans of care
            service developed to promote safe, proper, and sustained use of prescribed respiratory
            therapy medications, equipment, and techniques in the home.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Home Health</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-home-health</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Neonatal/Pediatric</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Neonatal/Pediatrics</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The care and treatment of premature infants, newborns and children. This
            includes management of mechanical ventilation, assessment, diagnostics and generalized
            respiratory treatments.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Neonatal/Pediatrics</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-neonatalpediatrics</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Function Technologist</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Function Technologists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>An individual who is trained and qualified to perform pulmonary diagnostic
            tests. In the course of conducting these tests, the Pulmonary Function Technologist is
            able to setup, calibrate, maintain, and ensure the quality assurance of the pulmonary
            function testing equipment. In the laboratory, clinical or patient care setting the
            technologist instructs patients, elicits cooperation, performs procedures, monitors
            patient response, and evaluates patient performance. Tests results are calculated,
            compared with predicted normal ranges, and evaluated for reliability. The technologist
            collects clinical history data and evaluates the clinical implications of the test
            results.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Function Technologist</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-pulmonary-function-technologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Preventive Medicine Clinical Informatic</actor>
        <actors>Preventive Medicine Clinical Informatics</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Physicians who practice Clinical Informatics collaborate with other health care
            and information technology professionals to analyze, design, implement and evaluate
            information and communication systems that enhance individual and population health
            outcomes, improve patient care, and strengthen the clinician-patient relationship.
            Clinical Informaticians use their knowledge of patient care combined with their
            understanding of informatics concepts, methods, and tools to: assess information and
            knowledge needs of health care professionals and patients; characterize, evaluate, and
            refine clinical processes; develop, implement, and refine clinical decision support
            systems; and lead or participate in the procurement, customization, development,
            implementation, management, evaluation, and continuous improvement of clinical
            information systems.
        </description>
        <name>Preventive Medicine Clinical Informatics</name>
        <uid>preventive-medicine-clinical-informatics</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>prosthetist</actor>
        <actors>prosthetists</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>A health care professional who is specifically educated and trained to manage
            comprehensive prosthetic patient care for individuals who have sustained complete or
            partial limb loss or absence. Prosthetists assess specific patient needs, formulate an
            appropriate treatment plan, implement the treatment plan and provide follow-up care.
        </description>
        <name>Prosthetist</name>
        <uid>prosthetist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Neuromuscular Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Neuromuscular Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A neurologist or child neurologist who specializes in the diagnosis and
            management of disorders of nerve, muscle or neuromuscular junction, including
            amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, peripheral neuropathies (e.g., diabetic and immune
            mediated neuropathies), various muscular dystrophies, congenital and acquired
            myopathies, inflammatory myopathies (e.g., polymyositis, inclusion body myositis) and
            neuromuscular transmission disorders (e.g., myasthenia gravis, Lambert-Eaton myasthenic
            syndrome).
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Neuromuscular Medicine</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-neuromuscular-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Pain Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Pain Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A neurologist, child neurologists or psychiatrist who provides a high level of
            care, either as a primary physician or consultant, for patients experiencing problems
            with acute, chronic or cancer pain in both hospital and ambulatory settings. Patient
            care needs may also be coordinated with other specialists.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Pain Medicine</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-pain-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Orthopedist</actor>
        <actors>Orthopedists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in surgery and treatment of musculoskeletal problems, including
            knees and spine.
        </description>
        <name>Orthopedic Surgery</name>
        <uid>orthopedic-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Orthotic Fitter</actor>
        <actors>Orthotic Fitters</actors>
        <category>services</category>
        <description>An individual trained in the management of fitting prefabricated orthoses.
        </description>
        <name>Orthotic Fitter</name>
        <uid>orthotic-fitter</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Orthopedic Physical Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Orthopedic Physical Therapists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in physical therapy of joints and muscles.</description>
        <name>Orthopedic Physical Therapy</name>
        <uid>orthopedic-physical-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Dentist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Dentists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's oral health.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Dentistry</name>
        <uid>pediatric-dentist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Urologist</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Urologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's genital and urinary problems.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Urology</name>
        <uid>pediatric-urologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatric Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Pediatric Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in complicated surgical conditions in children.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Surgery</name>
        <uid>pediatric-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatrics Hospice and Palliative Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Pediatrics Hospice and Palliative Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A pediatrician with special knowledge and skills to prevent and relieve the
            suffering experienced by patients with life-limiting illnesses. This specialist works
            with an interdisciplinary hospice or palliative care team to maximize quality of life
            while addressing physical, psychological, social and spiritual needs of both patient and
            family throughout the course of the disease, through the dying process, and beyond for
            the family. This specialist has expertise in the assessment of patients with advanced
            disease; the relief of distressing symptoms; the coordination of interdisciplinary
            patient and family-centered care in diverse venues; the use of specialized care systems
            including hospice; the management of the imminently dying patient; and legal and ethical
            decision making in end-of-life care.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatrics Hospice and Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>pediatrics-hospice-and-palliative-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pediatrics Medical Toxicology</actor>
        <actors>Pediatrics Medical Toxicologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Medical toxicologists are physicians that specialize in the prevention,
            evaluation, treatment and monitoring of injury and illness from exposures to drugs and
            chemicals, as well as biological and radiological agents. Medical toxicologists care for
            people in clinical, academic, governmental and public health settings, and provide
            poison control center leadership. Important areas of medical toxicology include acute
            drug poisoning, adverse drug events, drug abuse, addiction and withdrawal, chemicals and
            hazardous materials, terrorism preparedness, venomous bites and stings, and
            environmental and workplace exposures.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatrics Medical Toxicology</name>
        <uid>pediatrics-medical-toxicology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Physical Therapy Assistant</actor>
        <actors>Physical Therapy Assistants</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>(1)Physical therapist assistants are skilled health care providers who are
            graduates of a physical therapist assistant associate degree program accredited by an
            agency recognized by the Secretary of the U.S. Department of Education or Council on
            Postsecondary Accreditation, who assists the physical therapist in providing physical
            therapy. The supervising physical therapist is directly responsible for the actions of
            the physical therapist assistant. The PTA performs physical therapy procedures and
            related tasks that have been selected and delegated by the supervising physical
            therapist. Duties of the PTA include assisting the physical therapist in implementing
            treatment programs, training patients in exercised and activities of daily living,
            conducting treatments, and reporting to the physical therapist on the patient's
            responses. In addition to direct patient care, the PTA may also perform such functions
            as patient transport, and clinic or equipment preparation and maintenance. Currently
            more than half of all states require PTAs to be licensed, registered or certified. (2)
            An individual who works under the supervision of a physical therapist to assist him or
            her in providing physical therapy services. A physical therapy assistant may, for
            instance, help patients follow an appropriate exercise program that will increase their
            strength, endurance, coordination, and range of motion and train patients to perform
            activities of daily life.
        </description>
        <name>Physical Therapy Assistant</name>
        <uid>physical-therapy-assistant</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Plastic Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Plastic Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in plastic and reconstructive surgery.</description>
        <name>Plastic and Reconstructive Surgery</name>
        <uid>plastic-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Pulmonologist</actor>
        <actors>Pulmonologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in lungs and airways.</description>
        <name>Pulmonary Disease</name>
        <uid>pulmonologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Rehabilitation Counselor Assistive Technology Practitioner</actor>
        <actors>Rehabilitation Counselor Assistive Technology Practitioners</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Rehabilitation Counselor Assistive Technology Practitioner</name>
        <uid>rehabilitation-counselor-assistive-technology-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Reproductive Endocrinologist</actor>
        <actors>Reproductive Endocrinologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in infertility and hormonal problems.</description>
        <name>Reproductive Endocrinology</name>
        <uid>reproductive-erndocrinologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Geriatric Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Geriatric Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Care of older patients who have age and/or disease related decremental
            pulmonary changes. Diagnosis and treatment is very important for this group since
            chronic lung disease is the major cause of morbidity and mortality among them.
            Furthermore, as this segment of the population increases, life expectancy is being
            extended.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Geriatric Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-geriatric-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Neonatal/Pediatric</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Neonatal/Pediatrics</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The care and treatment of premature infants, newborns and children. This
            includes management of mechanical ventilation, assessment, diagnostics and generalized
            respiratory treatments.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Neonatal/Pediatrics</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-neonatalpediatrics</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Function Technologist</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Function Technologists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>An individual who is trained and qualified to perform pulmonary diagnostic
            tests. In the course of conducting these tests, the Pulmonary Function Technologist is
            able to setup, calibrate, maintain, and ensure the quality assurance of the pulmonary
            function testing equipment. In the laboratory, clinical or patient care setting the
            technologist instructs patients, elicits cooperation, performs procedures, monitors
            patient response, and evaluates patient performance. Tests results are calculated,
            compared with predicted normal ranges, and evaluated for reliability. The technologist
            collects clinical history data and evaluates the clinical implications of the test
            results.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered Pulmonary Function Technologist</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered-pulmonary-function-technologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Palliative/Hospice</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Palliative/Hospices</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A coordinated plan of care to help dying patients and their families handle the
            burden of terminal care. Effective secretion management and relief of dyspnea are
            paramount in caring for patients with end-stage pulmonary disease.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Palliative/Hospice</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-palliativehospice</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Rehabilitation</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Rehabilitations</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The respiratory therapist can assist the chronic pulmonary patient in returning
            to an optimal role in society by providing an effective program. It includes
            bronchopulmonary drainage, exercise therapy, and patient education.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Pulmonary Rehabilitation</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-pulmonary-rehabilitation</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Registered</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Registereds</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>A Registered Respiratory Therapist (RRT) is an advanced therapist who has
            passed standardized written and clinical simulation examinations administered by the
            National Board for Respiratory Care (NBRC). In addition, to the certified therapist
            (CRT) entry level skills, RRTs have advanced education and training in patient
            assessment, in the development and modification of patient care plans, and in assuring
            the appropriate utilization of respiratory care resources. An RRT is a graduate of an
            associate or baccalaureate degree producing educational programs approved by the
            Commission on Accreditation of Allied Health Education Programs (CAAHEP) and where
            applicable, is licensed by the state and is practicing within the scope of that license.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Registered</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-registered</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Emergency Care</actor>
        <actors>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Emergency Cares</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The immediate availability of diagnostic and therapeutic cardiopulmonary
            services in the assessment and management of trauma victims, patients requiring airway
            management and others requiring emergency care.
        </description>
        <name>Respiratory Therapist, Certified Emergency Care</name>
        <uid>respiratory-therapist-certified-emergency-care</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sleep Medicine Otolaryngologist</actor>
        <actors>Sleep Medicine Otolaryngologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in sleep disorders.</description>
        <name>Otolaryngologic Sleep Medicine</name>
        <uid>sleep-medicine-otolaryngologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist Orthoptist</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologist Orthoptists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist Orthoptist</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist-orthoptist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Thermography Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Thermography Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Thermography</name>
        <uid>thermography-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Surgery of the Hand</actor>
        <actors>Surgery of the Hands</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A surgeon with expertise in the investigation, preservation and restoration by
            medical, surgical and rehabilitative means, of all structures of the upper extremity
            directly affecting the form and function of the hand and wrist.
        </description>
        <name>Surgery of the Hand</name>
        <uid>surgery-surgery-of-the-hand</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Technician/Technologist</actor>
        <actors>Technician/Technologists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>A broad category grouping different kinds of technologists and technicians. See
            individual definitions.
        </description>
        <name>Technician/Technologist</name>
        <uid>techniciantechnologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Specialist/Technologist Rehabilitation, Blind</actor>
        <actors>Specialist/Technologist Rehabilitation, Blinds</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Definition to come...</description>
        <name>Specialist/Technologist Rehabilitation, Blind</name>
        <uid>specialisttechnologist-rehabilitation-blind</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sport Medicine Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Sport Medicine Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the prevention and treatment of sports injuries in children.
        </description>
        <name>Pediatric Sport Medicine</name>
        <uid>sport-medicine-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sports Medicine Physiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Sports Medicine Physiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in treating patients with sport related physical disabilities.
        </description>
        <name>Physiastric Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>sports-medicine-physiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sports Podiatrist</actor>
        <actors>Sports Podiatrists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in sport related foot and ankle problems.</description>
        <name>Sports Medicine Podiatry</name>
        <uid>sports-podiatrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sports Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Sports Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in prevention and treatment of sports related injuries.
        </description>
        <name>Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>sports-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Sleep Medicine Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Sleep Medicine Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's sleep disorders.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Sleep Medicine</name>
        <uid>sleep-medicine-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Transplant Hepatologist</actor>
        <actors>Transplant Hepatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in liver transplants.</description>
        <name>Transplant Hepatology</name>
        <uid>transplant-hepatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Addiction Counselor</actor>
        <actors>Addiction Counselors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in addiction counseling.</description>
        <name>Addiction Counseling</name>
        <uid>addiction-counselor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Addiction Specialist</actor>
        <actors>Addiction Specialists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the treatment of addiction disorders.</description>
        <name>Addiction Medicine</name>
        <uid>addiction-specialist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Adult Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Adult Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in adult's health.</description>
        <name>Adult Health Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>adult-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Advanced Dental Therapist(ADT)</actor>
        <actors>Advanced Dental Therapist(ADT)S</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>An Advanced Practice Dental Therapist is:&lt;br/&gt;(1) A dental therapist who
            has completed additional training beyond basic dental therapy education and provides
            dental services in accordance with state advanced practice dental therapist laws or
            statutes; or&lt;br/&gt;(2) A dental hygienist with a graduate degree in advanced dental
            therapy prepared for independent and interdependent decision making and direct
            accountability for clinical judgment across the dental health care continuum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The
            individual has been authorized by the relevant state board or a tribal entity to provide
            services under the remote supervision of a dentist. The functions of the advanced
            practice dental therapist vary based on the needs of the dentist, the educational
            preparation of the advanced practice dental therapist and state dental practice acts and
            regulations.
        </description>
        <name>Advanced Practice Dental Therapist</name>
        <uid>advanced-practice-dental-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Adult Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Adult Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in adult counceling and therapy.</description>
        <name>Adult Development &amp; Aging Psychology</name>
        <uid>adult-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Chemical Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Chemical Pathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in biochemistry of the human body.</description>
        <name>Chemical Pathology</name>
        <uid>chemical-pathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Child Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Child Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's psychological counceling and therapy.</description>
        <name>Clinical Child &amp; Adolescent Psychology</name>
        <uid>clinical-child-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractics</name>
        <uid>chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dance Therapist</actor>
        <actors>Dance Therapists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>The dance therapist, sometimes called a movement therapist, focuses on rhythmic
            body movements as a medium of physical and psychological change. Dance therapy is
            practiced more often with mental health patients than with physically disabled patients.
            A master's degree is required by the American Dance Therapy Association to award the
            credentials Dance Therapist Registered (DTR).
        </description>
        <name>Dance Therapist</name>
        <uid>dance-therapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Bariatric Medicine OBGYN</actor>
        <actors>Bariatric Medicine OBGYNS</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the treatment of obesity and its associated conditions.
        </description>
        <name>Bariatric Medicine OBGYN</name>
        <uid>bariatric-medicine-obgyn</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Assistant, Podiatric</actor>
        <actors>Assistant, Podiatrics</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An individual who assists a podiatrist in tasks, such as exposing and
            developing x-rays; taking and recording patient histories; assisting in biomechanical
            evaluations and negative castings; preparing and sterilizing instruments and equipment;
            providing the patient with postoperative instructions; applying surgical dressings;
            preparing the patient for treatment, padding, and strapping; and performing routine
            office procedures.
        </description>
        <name>Assistant, Podiatric</name>
        <uid>assistant-podiatric</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Audiologist</actor>
        <actors>Audiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in hearing and hearing aids.</description>
        <name>Audiology</name>
        <uid>audiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hospice and Palliative OBGYN</actor>
        <actors>Hospice and Palliative OBGYNS</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in preventing and relieving life limiting illnesses</description>
        <name>Hospice &amp; Palliative Medicine</name>
        <uid>hospice-palliative-obgyn</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Infectious Disease Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Infectious Disease Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in infectious diseases of all types and in all organ systems.
        </description>
        <name>Infectious Disease</name>
        <uid>infectious-disease-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Infectious Disease Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Infectious Disease Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in children's infectious diseases.</description>
        <name>Pediatric Infectious Disease</name>
        <uid>infectious-diseases-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Dentist</actor>
        <actors>Dentists</actors>
        <category>dental</category>
        <description>Specializes in teeth and oral health.</description>
        <name>General Dentistry</name>
        <uid>general-dentist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Gerontology Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Gerontology Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnosis of common illnesses.</description>
        <name>Gerontology Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>gerontology-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Geriatric Medicine Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Geriatric Medicine Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the aging process and elderly.</description>
        <name>Geriatric Medicine</name>
        <uid>geriatric-medicine-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Gynecologic Oncologist</actor>
        <actors>Gynecologic Oncologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in cancer and other tumors of the female reproductive organs.
        </description>
        <name>Gynecologic Oncology</name>
        <uid>gynecologic-oncologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Electrodiagnostic Physician</actor>
        <actors>Electrodiagnostic Physicians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Electrodiagnostic medicine is the medical subspecialty that applies
            neurophysiologic techniques to diagnose, evaluate, and treat patients with impairments
            of the neurologic, neuromuscular, and/or muscular systems. Qualified physicians are
            trained in performing electrophysiological testing and interpretation of the test data.
            They require knowledge in anatomy, physiology, kinesiology, histology, and pathology of
            the brain, spinal cord, autonomic nerves, cranial nerves, peripheral nerves,
            neuromuscular junction, and muscles. They must know clinical features and treatment of
            diseases of the central, peripheral, and autonomic nervous systems, as well as those of
            neuromuscular junction and muscle. Physicians also require special knowledge about
            electric signal processing, including waveform analysis, electronics and
            instrumentation, stimulation and recording equipment, and statistics.
        </description>
        <name>Electrodiagnostic Medicine</name>
        <uid>electrodiagnostic-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Forensic Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Forensic Pathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in investigating reasons of death.</description>
        <name>Forensic Pathology</name>
        <uid>forensic-pathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hematopathologist</actor>
        <actors>Hematopathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of blood cells and bone marrow.</description>
        <name>Hematology</name>
        <uid>hematopathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hand Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Hand Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in hand and wrist surgery.</description>
        <name>Hand Surgery</name>
        <uid>hand-orthopedist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hepatologist</actor>
        <actors>Hepatologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in liver and spleen diseases.</description>
        <name>Hepatology</name>
        <uid>hepatologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Low Vision</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Low Visions</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapists enable children and adults with visual impairment to
            engage in their chosen daily living activities safely and as independently as possible.
            This is accomplished by 1) teaching the person to use their remaining vision as
            efficiently as possible to complete activities; (2) modifying activities so that they
            can be completed with less vision; (3) training the person in use of adaptive equipment
            to compensate for vision loss, including high and low technology assistive devices; and
            (4) modifying the person's environment.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Low Vision</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-low-vision</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Mental Health</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Mental Healths</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapists provide treatment for people recovering from a mental
            or physical illness to regain their independence and stability and to engage in normal
            daily occupations (work, home, family life, school, leisure). Occupational therapists
            provide particular emphasis on interventions that result in improved quality of life and
            decrease hospitalization.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Mental Health</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-mental-health</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Pediatric</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Pediatrics</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapists provide services to infants, toddlers and children who
            have or who are at risk for developmental delays or disabilities. Occupational therapy
            is concerned with a child's ability to participate in daily life activities or
            "occupations." Occupational therapists use their unique expertise to help children with
            social-emotional, physical, cognitive, communication, and adaptive behavioral challenges
            and to help children to be prepared for and perform important learning and
            school-related activities and to fulfill their rule as students. Through an
            understanding of the impact of disability, illness, and impairment on a child's
            development, plan, ability to learn new skills, and overall occupational performance,
            occupational therapists design interventions that promote healthy development, establish
            needed skills, and/or modify environments, all in support of participation in daily
            activities.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Pediatrics</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-pediatrics</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Clinical Cardiac Electrophysiology</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Clinical Cardiac Electrophysiologies</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A field of special interest within the subspecialty of cardiovascular disease,
            specialty of Internal Medicine, which involves intricate technical procedures to
            evaluate heart rhythms and determine appropriate treatment for them.
        </description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Clinical Cardiac Electrophysiology</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-clinical-cardiac-electrophysiology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Hematologist</actor>
        <actors>Hematologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An internist with additional training who specializes in diseases of the blood,
            spleen and lymph. This specialist treats conditions such as anemia, clotting disorders,
            sickle cell disease, hemophilia, leukemia and lymphoma.
        </description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Hematology</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-hematology</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Internal Medicine Hypertension Specialist</actor>
        <actors>Internal Medicine Hypertension Specialists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A Hypertension Specialist is a physician who concentrates on all aspects of the
            diagnosis and treatment of hypertension.
        </description>
        <name>Internal Medicine Hypertension Specialist</name>
        <uid>internal-medicine-hypertension-specialist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Kinesiotherapist</actor>
        <actors>Kinesiotherapists</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>A provider trained and educated in the applied science of medically prescribed
            therapeutic exercise, education and adapted physical activities designed to improve the
            quality of line and health of adults and children by developing physical fitness,
            increasing mobility and independence, and improving psychosocial behavior. The
            kinesiotherapist seeks a coach-player relationship in which he/she helps the
            patient/client reach the goal of becoming an independent, self-sustaining person.
            Kinesiotherapists, as compared with physical therapists, put more emphasis on geriatric
            care, reconditioning and fitness, and psychiatric care. A large percentage of
            kinesiotherapists practice in Veterans Administration hospitals.
        </description>
        <name>Kinesiotherapist</name>
        <uid>kinesiotherapist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>OBGYN Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>OBGYN Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the care of the female reproductive system.</description>
        <name>OBGYN Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>obgyn-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Occupational Health</name>
        <uid>occupational-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Therapist Driving and Community Mobility</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Therapist Driving and Community Mobilities</actors>
        <category>therapy</category>
        <description>Occupational therapists can optimize and prolong an older driver's ability to
            drive safely and ease the transition to other forms of transportation if driving
            cessation becomes necessary. By identifying strengths as well as physical or cognitive
            challenges, occupational therapists can evaluate an individual's overall ability to
            operate a vehicle safely and recommend assistive devices or behavioral changes to limit
            risks. Occupational therapy practitioners offer a continuum of services related to
            community mobility, from evaluation of driving performance, through counseling and
            support for lifestyle changes, to maintaining independence and quality of life.
        </description>
        <name>Occupational Therapist Driving and Community Mobility</name>
        <uid>occupational-therapist-driving-and-community-mobility</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Molecular Genetic Pathologist</actor>
        <actors>Molecular Genetic Pathologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in laboratory tests of genetic materials.</description>
        <name>Molecular Genetic Pathology</name>
        <uid>molecular-genetic-pathologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neonatal &amp; Perinatal Pediatrician</actor>
        <actors>Neonatal &amp; Perinatal Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in premature and ill new borns as well as high-risk pregnancies.
        </description>
        <name>Neonatal &amp; Perinatal Medicine</name>
        <uid>neonatal-perinatal-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neonatal Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Neonatal Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in premature and ill new borns as well as high-risk pregnancies.
        </description>
        <name>Neonatology Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>neonatal-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Neuromusculoskeletal Medicine, Sports Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Neuromusculoskeletal Medicine, Sports Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Definition to come.</description>
        <name>Neuromusculoskeletal Medicine, Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>neuromusculoskeletal-medicine-sports-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Naturopathic Doctor</actor>
        <actors>Naturopathic Doctors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternative natural healing.</description>
        <name>Naturopath</name>
        <uid>naturopathic-doctor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Mental Retardation Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Mental Retardation Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the counceling and therapy of the mentally challenged.
        </description>
        <name>Mental Retardation &amp; Developmental Disabilities</name>
        <uid>mental-retardation-psychologists</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Obstetrician</actor>
        <actors>Obstetricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in pregnancy and delivery.</description>
        <name>Obstetrics</name>
        <uid>obstetrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Nutrition Chiropractor</actor>
        <actors>Nutrition Chiropractors</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in alternartive therapy of muscles, bones, and joints.
        </description>
        <name>Chiropractic Nutrition Medicine</name>
        <uid>nutrition-chiropractor</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Occupational Vision Optometrist</actor>
        <actors>Occupational Vision Optometrists</actors>
        <category>vision</category>
        <description>Specializes in work related vision and eye safety.</description>
        <name>Occupational Vision</name>
        <uid>occupational-vision-optometrist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Sports Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Sports Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A psychiatrist or neurologist who specializes in the diagnosis and treatment of
            sports related conditions and injuries.
        </description>
        <name>Psychiatry &amp; Neurology Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>psychiatry-neurology-sports-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Geneticist</actor>
        <actors>Geneticists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnoses of and counselling for genetic disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Ph.D. Medical Genetics</name>
        <uid>medical-geneticist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Medical Psychologist</actor>
        <actors>Medical Psychologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in treating the mind with medication.</description>
        <name>Prescribing (Medical) Psychology</name>
        <uid>medical-psychologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Vascular &amp; Interventional Radiologist</actor>
        <actors>Vascular &amp; Interventional Radiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in diagnosing diseases by imaging.</description>
        <name>Vascular &amp; Interventional Radiology</name>
        <uid>vascular-interventional-radiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Vascular Surgeon</actor>
        <actors>Vascular Surgeons</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in blood vessel surgery excluding the heart.</description>
        <name>Vascular Surgery</name>
        <uid>vascular-surgeon</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Neurophysiologist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Neurophysiologists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in nervous system disorders.</description>
        <name>Clinical Neurophysiology</name>
        <uid>clinical-neurophysiologist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Women's Health Nurse Practitoner</actor>
        <actors>Women's Health Nurse Practitoners</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in women's health.</description>
        <name>Women's Health Nurse Practitioner</name>
        <uid>women-health-nurse-practitioner</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Emergency Medicine Emergency Medical Service</actor>
        <actors>Emergency Medicine Emergency Medical Services</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An emergency medicine physician who specializes in non-hospital based emergency
            medical services (e.g., disaster site, accident scene, transport vehicle, etc.) to
            provide pre-hospital assessment, treatment, and transport patients.
        </description>
        <name>Emergency Medicine Emergency Medical Services</name>
        <uid>emergency-medicine-emergency-medical-services</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Child Abuse Pediatricians</actor>
        <actors>Child Abuse Pediatricians</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in treating consequences of child abuse and neglect.</description>
        <name>Child Abuse Pediatrics</name>
        <uid>child-abuse-pediatrician</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Clinical Biochemical Geneticist</actor>
        <actors>Clinical Biochemical Geneticists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in biochemical diagnostics of genetic disorders.</description>
        <name>Clinical Biochemical Genetics</name>
        <uid>clinical-biochemical-geneticist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Emergency Medicine Sports Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Emergency Medicine Sports Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>An emergency physician with special knowledge in sports medicine is responsible
            for continuous care in the field of sports medicine, not only for the enhancement of
            health and fitness, but also for the prevention and management of injury and illness. A
            sports medicine physician has knowledge and experience in the promotion of wellness and
            the role of exercise in promoting a healthy lifestyle. Knowledge of exercise physiology,
            biomechanics, nutrition, psychology, physical rehabilitation and epidemiology is
            essential to the practice of sports medicine.
        </description>
        <name>Emergency Medicine Sports Medicine</name>
        <uid>emergency-medicine-sports-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Geneticist</actor>
        <actors>Geneticists</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Specializes in the diagnoses of and counselling for genetic disorders.
        </description>
        <name>Clinical Genetics (M.D.)</name>
        <uid>clinical-geneticist</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Emergency Medicine Undersea and Hyperbaric Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Emergency Medicine Undersea and Hyperbaric Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A specialist who treats decompression illness and diving accident cases and
            uses hyperbaric oxygen therapy to treat such conditions as carbon monoxide poisoning,
            gas gangrene, non-healing wounds, tissue damage from radiation and burns, and bone
            infections. This specialist also serves as a consultant to other physicians in all
            aspects of hyperbaric chamber operations, and assesses risks and applies appropriate
            standards to prevent disease and disability in divers and other persons working in
            altered atmospheric conditions.
        </description>
        <name>Emergency Medicine Undersea and Hyperbaric Medicine</name>
        <uid>emergency-medicine-undersea-and-hyperbaric-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Medicine Addiction Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Family Medicine Addiction Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>A family medicine physician who specializes in the diagnosis and treatment of
            addictions.
        </description>
        <name>Family Medicine Addiction Medicine</name>
        <uid>family-medicine-addiction-medicine</uid>
    </element>
    <element>
        <actor>Family Medicine Adult Medicine</actor>
        <actors>Family Medicine Adult Medicines</actors>
        <category>medical</category>
        <description>Definition to come.</description>
        <name>Family Medicine Adult Medicine</name>
        <uid>family-medicine-adult-medicine</uid>
    </element>
</Specialties>

